<item>
<title>A Bug's Life</title>
<summary>Storyline
At an annual pace, a huge colony of ants is forced to collect every piece of food that grows on their island for a group of menacing grasshoppers. But that all changes when a misfit inventor ant named Flik accidentally knocks over the offering pile thus forcing the grasshoppers' devious leader Hopper to force the ants to redo their gathering of food. Despite the fact that his friends don't believe him and desperate to help save the colony, Flik volunteers to go out into the world and search for a group of 'warrior' bugs. Instead, what he got was a talented group of circus performers. But when the grasshoppers return and take control of the island, Flik must prove himself a true hero before it's too late.
U | 1h 35min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 5 February 1999</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/A%20Bug%27s%20Life%20%281998%29/A.Bugs.Life.1998.720p.BluRay.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNThmZGY4NzgtMTM4OC00NzNkLWEwNmEtMjdhMGY5YTc1NDE4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTgwNTQxNzM4NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTE4ODAyNw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,924_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Dog's Way Home</title>
<summary>Storyline
A female dog travels four hundred miles in search of her owner throughout a Colorado wilderness.
PG | 1h 36min | Adventure, Drama, Family | 25 January 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/a/A.Dogs.Way.Home.2019.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5MjcwMzY5OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDM0OTI1NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjAyNGYwZGEtYWYxOS00N2UzLWI0MWUtM2YzM2YxMzQ5MjFjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkzNDYzNTk@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aladdin</title>
<summary>Storyline
Aladdin is a poor street urchin who spends his time stealing food from the marketplace in the city of Agrabah. His adventures begin when he meets a young girl who happens to be Princess Jasmine, who is forced to be married by her wacky yet estranged father. Aladdin's luck suddenly changes when he retrieves a magical lamp from the Cave of Wonders. What he unwittingly gets is a fun-loving genie who only wishes to have his freedom. Little do they know is that the Sultan's sinister advisor Jafar has his own plans for both Aladdin and the lamp.
U | 1h 30min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 17 November 1993</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/Aladdin%20%281992%29/Aladdin.1992.720p.BRrip.x264.GAZ.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWFlN2VkZDQtNWY2NC00MTRmLTljMWMtOGZlNGM4ODZkNDU5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjY5NDU4NzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgzNDI3ODUyMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDg4MjY5NzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1416,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aladdin</title>
<summary>Storyline
A kindhearted street urchin and a power-hungry Grand Vizier vie for a magic lamp that has the power to make their deepest wishes come true.
PG | 2h 8min | Adventure, Comedy, Family | 22 May 2019</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Aladdin.2019.480p.PAHE.Film2Media.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Aladdin.2019.720p.x265.PAHE.Film2Media.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Aladdin.2019.720p.MkvCage.mkv(link 3 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Aladdin.2019.1080p.x265.RMT.mkv(link 4 | 1080P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Aladdin.2019.1080p.6CH.MkvCage.mkv(link 5 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjQ2ODIyMjY4MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzY4ODI2NzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWU0ZmRmOTctZGZlYy00ODM2LTlkYzItNjBiYmEwMmMyZmFkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODQzNTE3ODc@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,736_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aliens Ate My Homework</title>
<summary>Storyline
Extraterrestrials invade Earth and a pair of middle schoolers hold the fate of the world in their hands in Aliens Ate My Homework, a delightfully comical intergalactic adventure from Universal 1440 and Lay-Carnagey Entertainment. Aliens Ate My Homework is based on the first book in the wildly successful Rod Allbright and the Galactic Patrol series. Written by internationally renowned author Bruce Coville, the four-part saga has sold over 17 million books worldwide and has been translated into 16 languages. When a tiny intergalactic starship crashes into the bedroom of 12-year-old Rod Allbright (Jayden Greig), it's the start of the adventure of a lifetime for him and his cousin Elspeth (Lauren McNamara). Enlisted by the extraterrestrial Galactic Patrol, a group of out-of-this-world lawmen, Rod and Elspeth must race to save the world from Total Planetary Disaster. The film features the voice of William Shatner ("Star Trek") as the intrepid intergalactic explorer known as Phil the Plant.
PG | 1h 30min | Adventure , Comedy , Family | Video 6 March 2018</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Hollywood/2018-v2/Aliens%20Ate%20My%20Homework%20%282018%29%20%5B1080p%5D%20BluRay/Aliens%20Ate%20My%20Homework%20%282018%29%20%5B1080p%5D%20BluRay.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNThmYzMxYmYtMTc3Ny00NTVlLWI1NWQtNmJiNWJhZDBiZDkyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTAzNDg1MA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,659,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjRkZjM1MmItY2QzYy00Mzc3LWFmMGYtMWY4M2Q0MjA4MjUzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTAzNDg1MA@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alvin And The Chipmunks</title>
<summary>Storyline
In a tree farm, three musically inclined chipmunks, Alvin, Simon and Theodore, find their tree cut down and sent to Los Angeles. Once there, they meet the frustrated songwriter David Seville, and despite a poor house wrecking first impression, they impress him with their singing talent. Seeing the opportunity for success, both human and chipmunks make a pact for them to sing his songs. While that ambition proves a frustrating struggle with the difficult trio, the dream does come true after all. However, that success presents its own trials as their unscrupulous record executive, Ian Hawke, plans to break up this family to exploit the boys. Can Dave and the Chipmunks discover what they really value amid the superficial glamor around them?
U | 1h 32min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 21 December 2007</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2007/Alvin%20and%20the%20Chipmunks%20%282007%29/Alvin.And.The.Chipmunks.2007.720p.BluRay.x264.%5BYTS.AG%5D.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjdmNWY4MjItMjBiMi00MWNiLWI0ZjctYzBjZmEzOGRmNTc5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,678,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg2MDM4NTYwNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNjQ5Nzc4._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alvin and the Chipmunks: The Squeakquel</title>
<summary>Storyline
After a concert mishap lands Dave in the hospital, Alvin, Simon, and Theodore end up in the care of Dave's twenty-something cousin Toby. When the Chipmunks put aside their stardom to return to school to win a annual "Battle of the Bands" competition to save the school's music program. But the boys meet their match with the Chipettes, Brittany, Jeanette, & Eleanor, who are working for the Chipmunks's ex-manager Ian Hawke. Romantic sparks and crazy mishaps happen when the Chipmunks and Chipettes square off.
U | 1h 28min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 21 December 2009</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2009/Alvin%20and%20the%20Chipmunks-The%20Squeakquel%20%282009%29/Alvin%20and%20the%20Chipmunks%20The%20Squeakquel%202009%20720p%20BluRay%20x264%20AC3%20-%20NBY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI0NTc3MjU5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODM4Nzg2Mg@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDg4NTk0MTIzNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDI0NDUwMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1249,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alvin and the Chipmunks: Chipwrecked</title>
<summary>Storyline
Playing around while aboard a cruise ship, the Chipmunks and Chipettes accidentally go overboard and end up marooned in a tropical paradise. They discover their new turf is not as deserted as it seems.
U | 1h 27min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 16 December 2011</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2011/Alvin%20and%20the%20Chipmunks-Chipwrecked%20%282011%29/Alvin.and.the.Chipmunks.Chip.Wrecked.2011.720p.BluRay.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTMyMTU3NTg5Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDMyMjc2NQ@@._V1.._.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTkwMTI2MjEwMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDEwMTMxNw@@._V1_SX1378_CR0,0,1378,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alvin and the Chipmunks: The Road Chip</title>
<summary>Edit
Storyline
Through a series of misunderstandings, Alvin, Simon and Theodore come to believe that Dave is going to propose to his new girlfriend in Miami...and dump them. They have three days to get to him and stop the proposal, saving themselves not only from losing Dave but possibly from gaining a terrible stepbrother.
U | 1h 32min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 12 February 2016</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2015/Alvin%20and%20the%20Chipmunks-The%20Road%20Chip%20%282015%29/Alvin.And.The.Chipmunks.The.Road.Chip.2015.720p.BRRip.800MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1NjQyNTkyOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzA3OTUyNzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGZkMGVjNTAtOTU0Ny00Zjk0LThmZDUtYTcyMjc1ZGExMjRmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzk4ODQyMDU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Monster In Paris</title>
<summary>Storyline
Paris, 1910. Emile, a shy movie projectionist, and Raoul, a colorful inventor, find themselves embarked on the hunt for a monster terrorizing citizens. They join forces with Lucille, the big-hearted star of the Rare Bird cabaret, an eccentric scientist and his irascible monkey to save the monster, who turns out to be an over-sized but harmless flea, from the city's ruthlessly ambitious police chief.
U | 1h 30min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 27 January 2012</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2011/A%20Monster%20in%20Paris%20%282011%29/A%20Monster%20In%20Paris%28%202011%29%20BRRip%20720p%20x264%20%5BDual%20Audio%5D%5BEnglish%20%2B%20Hindi%5D.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZThiNDI3MWEtYmU5OS00ZGRlLWE0YmMtMGFlY2Y1MTU4NGIxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,708,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTA3MjI4NTU0MzheQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU3MDgzNzc0NDc@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Storks Journey</title>
<summary>Storyline
Orphaned at birth and raised by storks, the teenage sparrow Richard believes he is one of them. But when the time comes to migrate to Africa, his stork family is forced to reveal his true identity and leave him behind in the forest, since he is not a migratory bird and would not survive the journey. Determined to prove he is a stork after all, Richard ventures south on his own. But only with the help of Olga, an eccentric owl with an imaginary friend and Kiki, a narcissistic, disco-singing parakeet, does he stand a chance to reach his goal and learn to accept who he really is.
PG | 1h 25min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 7 September 2018</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/A%20Stork%27s%20Journey%20%282017%29/A.Storks.Journey.2017.720p.BRRip.750MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTFhYjJhMzctMWI2NC00ODRiLWE0YmItODBlYWJkNTU4NjgxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTE2MTYxOQ@@._V1_SX699_CR0,0,699,999_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzlmMzc0ZDgtMDhlZC00MDA3LWIwOWUtNjdmYjQwMTNjMDcxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc5OTMwOTQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Beauty and the Beast</title>
<summary>Storyline
Having lived a life in selfishness, a young prince is cursed by a mysterious enchantress to having the appearance of a monstrous beast. His only hope is to learn to love a young woman and earn her love in return in order to redeem himself. Years later, his chance shows itself when a young maiden named Belle offers to take her ill father's place as his prisoner. With help from the castle's enchanted staff, Belle learns to appreciate her captor and immediately falls in love with him. Back in the village however, an unscrupulous hunter has his own plans for Belle.
U | 1h 24min | Animation, Family, Fantasy | 9 October 1992</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/Beauty%20and%20the%20Beast%20%281991%29/Beauty%20and%20the%20Beast%201991.EXTENDED.720p.BrRip.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDJhNDgyY2YtNmEyNC00MjU0LTk5MmEtYmFjOTdlODdkNjk0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,670,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTIzMzMyNzcxNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTE1ODAyNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1362,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bee Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
When the bee Barry B. Benson graduates from college, he finds that he will have only one job for his entire life, and absolutely disappointed, he joins the team responsible for bringing the honey and pollination of the flowers to visit the world outside the hive. Once in Manhattan, he is saved by the florist Vanessa and he breaks the bee law to thank Vanessa. They become friends and Barry discovers that humans exploit bees to sell the honey they produce. Barry decides to sue the human race, with destructive consequences to nature.
U | 1h 31min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 14 December 2007</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2007/Bee%20Movie%20%282007%29/Bee%20Movie%20%282007%29%20720p%20BRRip%20%5BDual%20Audio%5D%20%5BEng-Hindi%5D.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE1MDYxOTA4MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDE0MDUzMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk0OTg2NjI5OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTgzMDUzMw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Big Hero 6</title>
<summary>Storyline
When a devastating event befalls the city of San Fransokyo and catapults Hiro into the midst of danger, he turns to Baymax and his close friends adrenaline junkie Go Go Tomago, neatnik Wasabi, chemistry whiz Honey Lemon and fanboy Fred. Determined to uncover the mystery, Hiro transforms his friends into a band of high-tech heroes called "Big Hero 6."
PG | 1h 42min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 30 January 2015</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/b/Big.Hero.6.2014.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMDliOTIzNmUtOTllOC00NDU3LWFiNjYtMGM0NDc1YTMxNjYxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3NzExMDQ@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,699,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTczMTk5NjQwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTAxNjI5MjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Captain Morten and the Spider Queen</title>
<summary>Storyline
Every ship deserves its captain.
1h 19min | Animation, Family | 15 August 2018</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/c/Captain.Morten.And.The.Spider.Queen.2018.720p.BrRip.ACOOL.FilmZone.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/c/Captain.Morten.And.The.Spider.Queen.2018.1080p.BrRip.ACOOL.FilmZone.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2EyMzA4Y2MtMzcwYS00YmFkLWI1MDUtNTQ3YzYxNzhiOGEwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjk4MzY1MTk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,706,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2EyMzA4Y2MtMzcwYS00YmFkLWI1MDUtNTQ3YzYxNzhiOGEwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjk4MzY1MTk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,706,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Captain Underpants: The Firt Epic Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
George and Harold are two imaginative pranksters who make the depressing Jerome Horwitz School a better place. They hypnotize their nemesis, the mean-spirited principal Mr. Krupp. He transforms into the incredibly clueless yet kind-hearted and enthusiastic superhero named Captain Underpants. Even without the mean principal, they discover that having Captain Underpants comes at a steep price. Meanwhile, Professor Poopypants tries to eliminate laughter with the school snitch Melvin, and George and Harold discover that there may be more to Mr. Krupp than they had originally thought.
U | 1h 29min | Animation, Action, Comedy | 24 July 2017</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/Captain%20Underpants-The%20First%20Epic%20Movie%20%282017%29/Captain.Underpants.The.First.Epic.Movie.2017.720p.BRRip.800MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMmQwMzdiOGMtNGZiYS00YjgyLWJlMjItYzQ3Nzc2OGIwYjQwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzQ1MTM3NjY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTgyNzY2OTU3Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTA4ODc5MDI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,974_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Cars</title>
<summary>Storyline
While traveling to California for the dispute of the final race of the Piston Cup against The King and Chick Hicks, the famous Lightning McQueen accidentally damages the road of the small town Radiator Springs and is sentenced to repair it. Lightning McQueen has to work hard and finds friendship and love in the simple locals, changing its values during his stay in the small town and becoming a true winner.
PG | 1h 57min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 28 July 2006</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/c/Cars.2006.720p.BrRip.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5NzY0MzA2MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNDc3NTc2._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzYxMjY5NDUyMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzgzMTQyMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1637,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Cars 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
The famous race car Lightning McQueen and his team are invited to compete in the World Grand Prix race. There, McQueen's best friend Mater finds himself involved in international espionage, and alongside two professional British spies attempts to uncover a secret plan led by a mysterious mastermind and his criminal gang, which threatens the lives of all competitors in the tournament.
U | 1h 46min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 22 July 2011</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/c/Cars.2.2011.720p.BrRip.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTUzNTc3MTU3M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzIxNTc3NA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjE4ODY5NjkyMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjg1NTMwNQ@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,742_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Cars 3</title>
<summary>Storyline
Blindsided by a new generation of blazing-fast racers, the legendary Lightning McQueen is suddenly pushed out of the sport he loves. To get back in the game, he will need the help of an eager young race technician with her own plan to win, inspiration from the late Fabulous Hudson Hornet, and a few unexpected turns. Proving that #95 isn't through yet will test the heart of a champion on Piston Cup Racing's biggest stage!
U | 1h 42min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 14 July 2017</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/c/Cars.3.2017.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc0NzU2OTYyN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTkwOTg2MTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzUwODE2NDY4Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODU5NDMwMTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1152,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Charming</title>
<summary>Storyline
Charming is an irreverent animated comedy about a young Prince with an irresistible appeal and one kick-ass maiden who wants him only for his money. Cursed as a child, Prince Philippe Charming compulsively proposes to every woman he encounters, leaving a trail of lovesick ladies and scorned lovers to wreak vengeful havoc on the Kingdom. Ultimately, Prince Philippe's exasperated father, King Charming, gives the young Prince an ultimatum... Find a true, true-love before his 21st Birthday or lose all claim to the throne.
1h 30min | Animation , Comedy , Family | 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/c/Charming.2018.720p.BrRip.RARBG.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjUwNTFiNjctZDE0NS00YmNmLWI3NTctNGY4MTRhZWVhNGI1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzYxNDg0NTg@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,672,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDc0ZmM0NTUtMTNhNC00MDg2LWI1YTMtYTU0YTdmOWY2NjY3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjczMzY3NDI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christopher Robin</title>
<summary>Storyline
An adult Christopher Robin, who is now focused on his new life, work, and family, suddenly meets his old friend Winnie the Pooh, who returns to his unforgotten childhood past to help him return to the Hundred Acre Wood and help find Pooh's lost friends.
PG | 1h 44min | Animation , Adventure , Comedy | 16 August 2018</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/New%20folder%2025/Christopher%20Robin%202018%20480p.Pahe.Film9.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/New%20folder%2025/Christopher.Robin.2018.720p.MkvCage.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/New%20folder%2025/Christopher.Robin.2018.1080p.6CH.MkvCage.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjAzOTM2OTAyNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTg5ODg1NTM@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2Y4YWU0ZmEtYjc0Mi00MjhiLTgyYzAtODFkMmJiMzg0YWJiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQxNjcxNQ@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,741_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>


<item>
<title>Cloudy With A Chance Of Meatballs</title>
<summary>Storyline
Flint Lockwood thinks he's a genius. But none of the things he invented are things that make sense or are useful. However, he has the support of his mother but when she dies, he's left alone with his father who thinks he should give it up. When the community that he lives in is in an economic crisis because their primary source of income, a sardine cannery, was shut down, Flint decides to try his latest invention, a machine that can turn water into food. But something goes wrong and the machine ends up in the atmosphere. Later it starts raining food. The shifty mayor tries to use this as a way to help their community, but when Flint senses something wrong with the machine, the mayor convinces him to ignore it. However, as Flint predicts, chaos ensues.
U | 1h 30min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 18 September 2009</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/c/Cloudy.With.A.Chance.Of.Meatballs.2009.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg0MjAwNDI5MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODkyMzg2Mg@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,672,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg1MDYwODU5MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjI5MjE4Mg@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Cloudy With A Chance Of Meatballs 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
After the disastrous food storm in the first film, Flint and his friends are forced to leave the town. Flint accepts the invitation from his idol Chester V to join The Live Corp Company, which has been tasked to clean the island, and where the best inventors in the world create technologies for the betterment of mankind. When Flint discovers that his machine still operates and now creates mutant food beasts like living pickles, hungry tacodiles, shrimpanzees and apple pie-thons, he and his friends must return to save the world.
U | 1h 35min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 25 October 2013</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/c/Cloudy.With.A.Chance.Of.Meatballs.2.2013.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTYzNDM0MDI1NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzQ5NzYxOQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3MjA5MTYwNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjUwMTYyMDE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,755_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Coco</title>
<summary>Storyline
Despite his family's baffling generations-old ban on music, Miguel dreams of becoming an accomplished musician like his idol, Ernesto de la Cruz. Desperate to prove his talent, Miguel finds himself in the stunning and colorful Land of the Dead following a mysterious chain of events. Along the way, he meets charming trickster Hector, and together, they set off on an extraordinary journey to unlock the real story behind Miguel's family history.
PG | 1h 45min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 19 January 2018</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2017/Coco.2017.480p.Pahe.Fardadl_co.mkv(link 1 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2017/Coco.2017.1080p.x265.RMTeam.Fardadl_co.mkv(link 2 | 1080P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2017/Coco.2017.1080p.6CH.MkvCage.Fardadl_co.mkv(link 2 | 1080P FULL HD)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYjQ5NjM0Y2YtNjZkNC00ZDhkLWJjMWItN2QyNzFkMDE3ZjAxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODIxMzk5NjA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,699,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTY2MTkzOTgyMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTQ5NDMwMTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1545,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Coraline</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Coraline moves to an old house, she feels bored and neglected by her parents. She finds a hidden door with a bricked up passage. During the night, she crosses the passage and finds a parallel world where everybody has buttons instead of eyes, with caring parents and all her dreams coming true. When the Other Mother invites Coraline to stay in her world forever, the girl refuses and finds that the alternate reality where she is trapped is only a trick to lure her.
PG | 1h 40min | Animation, Drama, Fantasy | 8 May 2009</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2009/Coraline%20%282009%29/Coraline.2009.BluRay.720p.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjM2NTVkYjctYTMxZi00OTVlLWEyNzMtODg4MDRkNjBhYjZhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjI4NDY5ODM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/obBsMjC9dkDeoYsLxHURikW87UZ.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Despicable Me</title>
<summary>Storyline
In a happy suburban neighborhood surrounded by white picket fences with flowering rose bushes, sits a black house with a dead lawn. Unbeknownst to the neighbors, hidden beneath this home is a vast secret hideout. Surrounded by a small army of minions, we discover Gru, planning the biggest heist in the history of the world. He is going to steal the moon. (Yes, the moon!) Gru delights in all things wicked. Armed with his arsenal of shrink rays, freeze rays, and battle-ready vehicles for land and air, he vanquishes all who stand in his way. Until the day he encounters the immense will of three little orphaned girls who look at him and see something that no one else has ever seen: a potential Dad. The world's greatest villain has just met his greatest challenge: three little girls named Margo, Edith and Agnes.
U | 1h 35min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 15 October 2010</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/d/Despicable.Me.2010.720p.BrRip.Ganool.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3NjY0MTQ0Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzQ2MTc0Mw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYjIzMmFkZWEtNjVlZC00OGQzLWFjOTAtNmQwMGU5YWJhNGFmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjI0OTE3Njc@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Despicable Me 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
While Gru, the ex-supervillain is adjusting to family life and an attempted honest living in the jam business, a secret Arctic laboratory is stolen. The Anti-Villain League decides it needs an insider's help and recruits Gru in the investigation. Together with the eccentric AVL agent, Lucy Wilde, Gru concludes that his prime suspect is the presumed dead supervillain, El Macho, whose his teenage son is also making the moves on his eldest daughter, Margo. Seemingly blinded by his overprotectiveness of his children and his growing mutual attraction to Lucy, Gru seems on the wrong track even as his minions are being quietly kidnapped en masse for some malevolent purpose.
U | 1h 38min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 28 June 2013</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/d/Despicable.Me.2.2013.720p.BrRip.Ganool.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjExNjAyNTcyMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODQzMjQ3MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWIzNTg0N2QtN2FmNC00MDc3LWEyMDgtNDIyYjgwMDhlZTY3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjk3NTUyOTc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Despicable Me 3</title>
<summary>Storyline
After he is fired from the Anti-Villain League for failing to take down the latest bad guy to threaten humanity, Gru finds himself in the midst of a major identity crisis. But when a mysterious stranger shows up to inform Gru that he has a long-lost twin brother-a brother who desperately wishes to follow in his twin's despicable footsteps-one former super-villain will rediscover just how good it feels to be bad.
U | 1h 29min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 30 June 2017</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/d/Despicable.Me.3.2017.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjUyNzQ2MTg3Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzE4NDM3MTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,631,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNGQxYjNkMjctZTc4ZC00ODc0LWFlYjItZGVlNWZjYWJmZGQxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTcxNTA4ODQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dolphin Tale</title>
<summary>Storyline
A lonely and friendless boy finds and untangles a hurt dolphin that is caught in a crab trap. He becomes very attached to the dolphin when the tail must be taken off to save the dolphin's life. The boy believes the dolphin would be able to swim normally if it was given a prosthetic tail.
U | 1h 53min | Drama, Family | 14 October 2011</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/d/Dolphin.Tale.2011.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk2NTQwMTU5NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTU0MzE0NQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY1OTQ3MzQyOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDk0NzE2Ng@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,948_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dolphin Tale 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
It has been several years since young Sawyer Nelson and the dedicated team at the Clearwater Marine Hospital, headed by Dr. Clay Haskett, rescued Winter. With the help of Dr. Cameron McCarthy, who developed a unique prosthetic tail for the injured dolphin, they were able to save her life. Yet their fight is not over. Winter's surrogate mother, the very elderly dolphin Panama, has passed away, leaving Winter without the only poolmate she has ever known. However, the loss of Panama may have even greater repercussions for Winter, who, according to USDA regulations, cannot be housed alone, as dolphins' social behavior requires them to be paired with other dolphins. Time is running out to find a companion for her before the team at Clearwater loses their beloved Winter to another aquarium.
U | 1h 47min | Drama, Family | 3 October 2014</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/d/Dolphin.Tale.2.2014.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA5NzE4ODQwMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTc4OTA5MTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE4NDE3OTE4OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTM0MjA1MjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1312,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dragon Ball Super: Broly</title>
<summary>Storyline
Goku and Vegeta encounter Broly, a Saiyan warrior unlike any fighter they've faced before.
PG | 1h 40min | Animation, Action, Fantasy | 23 January 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/d/Dragon.Ball.Super.Broly.2018.720p.BrRip.GalaxyRG.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg0YzM2NzMtOGM1OC00MzlkLWI1NDEtYTI2MGZkZGJlYWQ0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQxNjcxNQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,715,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg0YzM2NzMtOGM1OC00MzlkLWI1NDEtYTI2MGZkZGJlYWQ0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQxNjcxNQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,715,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Duck Duck Goose</title>
<summary>Storyline
Peng is a freewheeling bachelor goose who'd rather do anything than practice for the upcoming migration. He thinks he's better than everyone else and spends his time attempting crazy stunts at even crazier speeds. In one such stunt, Peng flies too near the ground, hits a flock of ducklings and separates brother and sister, Chao and Chi, from the rest. In this unlikely meeting, Peng will begin a journey that will break his wing and nearly break his heart as he grows to understand the power of unconditional love in the form of two ducklings, who likewise grow to see him as the best father they could ever have.
PG | 1h 31min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 30 March 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/d/Duck.Duck.Goose.2018.720p.BrRip.nItRo.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjljMWMyMDItMTU4NS00OTY4LWI5NTItNjRjNjM2YTU1OWQwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjEyMzc1Njg@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,682,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYmYzODQ4YjktYTI0OC00OGI2LTkyN2YtYTYwZTkzOTRkYzgyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjM4NTM5NDY@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,744_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Dumbo</title>
<summary>Storyline
Holt was once a circus star, but he went off to war and when he returned it had terribly altered him. Circus owner Max Medici (Danny DeVito) hires him to take care of Dumbo, a newborn elephant whose oversized ears make him the laughing stock of the struggling circus troupe. But when Holt's children discover that Dumbo can fly, silver-tongued entrepreneur V.A. Vandevere (Michael Keaton), and aerial artist Colette Marchant (Eva Green) swoop in to make the little elephant a star.
PG | 1h 52min | Family, Fantasy | 29 March 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/d/Dumbo.2019.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjMxMDE0MDI1Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzExNTU3NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGI4YWZiYzctODVhMS00OGNmLThjZDctYWFkOTgzM2YyYjE4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjA0NzcwMjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1747,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Early Man</title>
<summary>Storyline
Set at the dawn of time, when prehistoric creatures and woolly mammoths roamed the earth, Early Man tells the story of Dug, along with sidekick Hognob as they unite his tribe against a mighty enemy Lord Nooth and his Bronze Age City to save their home.
PG | 1h 29min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 26 January 2018 (UK)</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/e/Early.Man.2018.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYWMxYWVjNzAtMTY0YS00YWQyLWExMGItMjUxODkwYzQyNzMwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjMxOTE0ODA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,657,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYjFlYTcyNWYtMjIwZC00NWJiLTkzYzYtZThiYjc5MTkyMjdjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzExMTY0MjU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Epic</title>
<summary>Storyline
Young Mary Katherine (M.K.) returns to her eccentric scientist father's home, but his all-consuming quest to discover a tiny civilization in the neighboring forest drives them apart. However, M.K. soon finds herself shrunken down by Queen Tara of that forest who was mortally wounded by the putrefying Boggans, and charged to deliver a pod bearing the new Queen to safety. Together with a veteran Leafman warrior, two goofy mollusks and a young maverick, M.K. agrees to help. As the villainous Boggan leader, Mandrake closes in, M.K. and her new friends must draw on the best of themselves together and discover what they have to save their world.
U | 1h 42min | Animation, Adventure, Family | 1 May 2013</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2013/Epic%20%282013%29/Epic.2013.720p.BluRay.x264.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTgyNDYwNzE5NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzUyODM5OA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,678,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTk1Nzg3NzU2Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjg0NDY3OA@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,753_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Escape From Planet Earth</title>
<summary>Storyline
The story takes place on planet Baab where admired astronaut Scorch Supernova (Brendan Fraser) is a national hero to the blue alien population. A master of daring rescues, Scorch pulls off astonishing feats with the quiet aid of his nerdy brother, Gary (Rob Corddry), head of mission control at BASA.
U | 1h 29min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 7 March 2014</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2013/Escape%20from%20Planet%20Earth%20%282013%29/Escape.from.Planet.Earth.2013.720p.BluRay.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQyMTk4NjkyMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzA2OTY4OA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTc1MjE0NTA3N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTE3OTMxODE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ferdinand</title>
<summary>Storyline
Destined to become a fearless fighting bull, the young pacifist and flower-loving calf, Ferdinand, summons up the courage to escape from a Spanish bull-training camp, to finally find himself on little Nina's idyllic and fragrant farm. However, an unfortunate run-in with a busy golden bee will send the immense but peaceful animal back to the old Casa del Toro academy, where the famous matador, El Primero, usually selects his worthy bovine opponents for the arena. Does Ferdinand hide a fierce champion underneath a mountain of muscles, or is he a gentle giant after all?
U | 1h 48min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 9 December 2017</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/f/Ferdinand.2017.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOTIwMDI0NjQ4OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjU0MzAyNDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzIwYjJhYzUtYTVmNi00ZmE4LWE0ZmQtMzUxMGVkOWM1YjQ0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDE5MTU2MDE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Finding Dory</title>
<summary>Storyline
Dory is a wide-eyed, blue tang fish who suffers from memory loss every 10 seconds or so. The one thing she can remember is that she somehow became separated from her parents as a child. With help from her friends Nemo and Marlin, Dory embarks on an epic adventure to find them. Her journey brings her to the Marine Life Institute, a conservatory that houses diverse ocean species.
U | 1h 37min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 29 July 2016</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/f/Finding.Dory.2016.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzg4MjM2NDQ4MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzk3MTgyODE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTFmMTY5NDQtMTAzNS00ZmM4LWEzYzctZTk0ZDZiMWE0ODE0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzg0NTE4MDQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Finding Nemo</title>
<summary>Storyline
A clown fish named Marlin lives in the Great Barrier Reef and loses his son, Nemo, after he ventures into the open sea, despite his father's constant warnings about many of the ocean's dangers. Nemo is abducted by a boat and netted up and sent to a dentist's office in Sydney. While Marlin ventures off to try to retrieve Nemo, Marlin meets a fish named Dory, a blue tang suffering from short-term memory loss. The companions travel a great distance, encountering various dangerous sea creatures such as sharks, anglerfish and jellyfish, in order to rescue Nemo from the dentist's office, which is situated by Sydney Harbour. While the two are searching the ocean far and wide, Nemo and the other sea animals in the dentist's fish tank plot a way to return to the sea to live their lives free again.
U | 1h 40min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 10 October 2003</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/f/Finding.Nemo.2003.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjMxYzBiNjUtZDliNC00MDAyLTg3N2QtOWNjNmNhZGQzNDg5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjE2MjQwNjc@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTcwMTU0NDU5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzUzOTAyNw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,960_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Flushed Away</title>
<summary>Storyline
Roddy is a decidedly upper-crust "society mouse" who lives the life of a beloved pet in a posh Kensington flat. When a sewer rat named Sid comes spewing out of the sink and decides he's hit the jackpot, Roddy schemes to rid himself of the pest by luring him into the "whirlpool." Sid may be an ignorant slob, but he's no fool, so it is Roddy who winds up being flushed away into the bustling sewer world of Ratropolis. There Roddy meets Rita, an enterprising scavenger who works the sewers in her faithful boat, the Jammy Dodger. Roddy immediately wants out, or rather, up; Rita wants to be paid for her trouble; and, speaking of trouble, the villainous Toad - who royally despises all rodents equally, making no distinction between mice and rats--wants them iced... literally. The Toad dispatches his two hapless hench-rats, Spike and Whitey, to get the job done. When they fail, the Toad has no choice but to send to France for his cousin - that dreaded mercenary, Le Frog.
U | 1h 25min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 1 December 2006</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2006/Flushed%20Away%20%282006%29/Flushed%20Away%202006%20HDRip%20H.264%20720.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTI1MzE1MDk2N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwMjEwMzI3._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjkyMzcwMTY4MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNDQwMzI3._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Frozen</title>
<summary>Storyline
Fearless optimist Anna teams up with rugged mountain man Kristoff and his loyal reindeer Sven and sets off on an epic journey to find her sister Elsa, whose icy powers have trapped the kingdom of Arendelle in eternal winter. Encountering Everest-like conditions, mystical trolls and a hilarious snowman named Olaf, Anna and Kristoff battle the elements in a race to save the kingdom. From the outside Elsa looks poised, regal and reserved, but in reality she lives in fear as she wrestles with a mighty secret: she was born with the power to create ice and snow. It's a beautiful ability, but also extremely dangerous. Haunted by the moment her magic nearly killed her younger sister Anna, Elsa has isolated herself, spending every waking minute trying to suppress her growing powers. Her mounting emotions trigger the magic, accidentally setting off an eternal winter that she can't stop. She fears she's becoming a monster and that no one, not even her sister, can help her.
PG | 1h 42min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 6 December 2013</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/f/Frozen.2013.720p.BrRip.Ganool.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1MjQwMTE5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjk3MTcyMDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWVlMTRkMGYtNjQ1Yy00YTViLWI5M2ItMjU4YjY3ZWQ2M2JmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjQ4ODE4MzQ@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,792_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Gnome Alone</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Chloe discovers that her new home's garden gnomes are not what they seem, she must decide between the pursuit of a desired high school life and taking up the fight against the Troggs.
PG | 1h 25min | Animation, Comedy, Fantasy | 2 November 2017</summary>
<link>http://dl.roozdl.com/roozdl/1397/3/Gnome_Alone_2017_720p_WEB-DL.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWIzMjcxMjgtMjM2NS00MjI5LTk4Y2UtYTU2MzdhMmQ2NmJmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzQxNDQ3MzA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTI5ZjhjYWUtNDFlYS00OTAxLTk2ZjEtMTQzODI0NDk3Yjg4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjkxMzgzODU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Goosebumps 2: Haunted Halloween</title>
<summary>Storyline
Two young friends find a magic book that brings a ventriloquist's dummy to life.
PG | 1h 30min | Adventure , Comedy , Family | 19 October 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/g/Goosebumps.2.Haunted.Halloween.2018.720p.BluRay.GECKOS.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzgxMDQ2MDUyMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzgyMjQyNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk4MDEzNDQxOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDc2Mzk4NTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Henchmen</title>
<summary>Storyline
In a world of super-villains, evil schemes and global domination, someone has to take out the trash. Welcome to the world of Henchmen, third class. When a fresh-faced new recruit joins the Union of Evil, he is assigned to a motley crew of blue-collar workers led by fallen henchmen Hank. But when The Kid accidentally steals the super villain's ultimate weapon, Hank must break his risk-nothing code to save the boy he's befriended, even if it means becoming the one thing he has always avoided being: a hero.
1h 29min | Animation, Comedy | 7 December 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/h/Henchmen.2018.720p.WEB-DL.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWNhYTY4YTAtZjE1ZC00MmVhLTkyMzMtMzBmM2RiNjU2MjBlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDc4MzI1NDM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2NlMDk1YjQtMjFmOC00MWE0LWI5ZDEtNWNkYjU0OTMwYzJjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDc4MzI1NDM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Hercules</title>
<summary>Storyline
Hercules, son of the Greek God, Zeus, is turned into a half-god, half-mortal by evil Hades, God of the Underworld, who plans to overthrow Zeus. Hercules is raised on Earth and retains his god-like strength, but when he discovers his immortal heritage Zeus tells him that to return to Mount Olympus he must become a true hero. Hercules becomes a famous hero with the help of his friend Pegasus and his personal trainer, Phil the satyr. Hercules battles monsters, Hades and the Titans, but it is his self-sacrifice to rescue his love Meg which makes him a true hero.
U | 1h 33min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 10 October 1997</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/1997/Hercules.1997.720p.ShAaNiG.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/1997/Hercules.1997.1080p.YIFY.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDcwYjEyNWItMGI1Mi00MjI1LWIyMDEtMTQ4YjhkNjM4NDU3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDUyOTg3Njg@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTJhODIzMDYtM2UxNC00N2M4LWI3MDMtNGEzYWZmNjNlYWJhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjQ4ODE4MzQ@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Hey Arnold: The Jungle Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
Picking up where Hey Arnold! (1994) left off, this tells the story of what happened to Arnold's parents.
PG | 1h 21min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | TV Movie 1 June 2018</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/Hey%20Arnold-The%20Jungle%20Movie%20%282017%29/Hey.Arnold.The.Jungle.Movie.2017.720p.HDTV.650MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzU3MDE4NTMtNDY3My00MWQ4LWEwZTQtMDA1NTE0NGQ5YTcyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzQ4MzcwODk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWI0NzYyNWMtMWQ1Mi00NjhiLTg5NDktYmY3MmQ0MDIzNmEyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzQ4MzcwODk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1538,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Home</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Oh, a loveable misfit from another planet, lands on Earth and finds himself on the run from his own people, he forms an unlikely friendship with an adventurous girl named Tip who is on a quest of her own. Through a series of comic adventures with Tip, Oh comes to understand that being different and making mistakes is all part of being human. And while he changes her planet and she changes his world, they discover the true meaning of the word HOME.
U | 1h 34min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 20 March 2015</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2015/Home%20%282015%29/Home.2015.720p.BluRay.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjExOTQ4MDMyMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTE3NDM2MzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA5NzIxMTMwMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzY5NTE5NDE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,962_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Hotel Transylvania</title>
<summary>Storyline
In 1895, Dracula builds a resort in Transylvania, hidden from the humans, to raise his beloved daughter Mavis in a safe environment. In the present, the place is the Hotel Transylvania, where monsters bring their families to vacation far from the frightening humans. Dracula invites his friends - Frankenstein and his wife Eunice; Wayne and Wanda, the werewolves; Griffin, the invisible man; Murray, the mummy; Bigfoot, among others - to celebrate the 118th birthday of Mavis. When the party is ready to start, the 21-year-old Jonathan is walking through the forest and stumbles upon the hotel. Dracula sees Jonathan and disguises him as a monster to hide Jonathan from the guests. But Mavis also sees Jonathan and Dracula forces him to pose as a monster. Soon Mavis believes that Jonathan is the "zing" of her life despite the advice of her father about humans.
U | 1h 31min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 12 October 2012</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/h/Hotel.Transylvania.2012.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTM3NjQyODI3M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDM4NjM0OA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjQzMTgxMTQ2NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDkxNTU0OA@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,959_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Hotel Transylvania 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
The Drac pack is back for an all-new monster comedy adventure in Sony Pictures Animation's Hotel Transylvania 2! Everything seems to be changing for the better at Hotel Transylvania... Dracula's rigid monster-only hotel policy has finally relaxed, opening up its doors to human guests. But behind closed coffins, Drac is worried that his adorable half-human, half-vampire grandson, Dennis, isn't showing signs of being a vampire. So while Mavis is busy visiting her human in-laws with Johnny - and in for a major cultural shock of her own - "Vampa" Drac enlists his friends Frank, Murray, Wayne and Griffin to put Dennis through a "monster-in-training" boot camp. But little do they know that Drac's grumpy and very old, old, old school dad Vlad is about to pay a family visit to the hotel. And when Vlad finds out that his great-grandson is not a pure blood - and humans are now welcome at Hotel Transylvania - things are going to get batty!
U | 1h 29min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 16 October 2015</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/h/Hotel.Transylvania.2.2015.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjEzNzc4NzEyMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTAxMDQ2NTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTY4NTQxOTMyM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDQ5OTA4NjE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,959_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Hotel Transylvania 3: Summer Vacation </title>
<summary>Storyline
Mavis surprises Dracula with a family voyage on a luxury Monster Cruise Ship so he can take a vacation from providing everyone else's vacation at the hotel. The rest of Drac's Pack cannot resist going along. But once they leave port, romance arises when Dracula meets the mysterious ship Captain, Ericka. Now it's Mavis' turn to play the overprotective parent, keeping her dad and Ericka apart. Little do they know that his "too good to be true" love interest is actually a descendant of Abraham Van Helsing, ancient nemesis to Dracula and all other monsters.
U | 1h 37min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 27 July 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/h/Hotel.Transylvania.3.Summer.Vacation.2018.720p.BrRip.RARBG.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjA1MzU5MTY3OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTU5MDA3NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE1MjA5NzQ5MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzUwMjA3NTM@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</title>
<summary>Storyline
As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless' discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup's reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind.
PG | 1h 44min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 1 February 2019</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/How.to.Train.Your.Dragon.The.Hidden.World.2019.480p.RMTeam.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/How.to.Train.Your.Dragon.The.Hidden.World.2019.720p.6CH.RARBG.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/How.to.Train.Your.Dragon.The.Hidden.World.2019.1080p.AC3.6CH.MkvCage.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjIwMDIwNjAyOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDE1MDc2NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,631,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzEyM2ZhNzktODI2Mi00NTQ1LWJkYTctZTc0Y2YxNGIwZDgzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTIwMDk4NDQ@._V1_SY1000_SX1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ice Age</title>
<summary>Storyline
Back when the Earth was being overrun by glaciers, and animals were scurrying to save themselves from the upcoming Ice Age, a sloth named Sid, a woolly mammoth named Manny, and a saber-toothed tiger named Diego are forced to become unlikely heroes. The three reluctantly come together when they have to return a human child to its father while braving the deadly elements of the impending Ice Age.
U | 1h 21min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 22 March 2002</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/i/Ice.Age.2002.720p.BrRip.Ganool.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMmYxZWY2NzgtYzJjZC00MDFmLTgxZTctMjRiYjdjY2FhODg3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjk1Njg5NTA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZGY2ZWZiMDgtNWM4Yi00ZDljLTgzN2EtOWViM2YwOWRjYTIyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODI3MTM2NDY@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,962_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ice Age 2: The Meltdown</title>
<summary>Storyline
Manny the woolly mammoth, Sid the sloth, Diego the saber-toothed tiger, and the hapless prehistoric squirrel/rat known as Scrat are still together and enjoying the perks of their now melting world. Manny may be ready to start a family, but nobody has seen another mammoth for a long time; Manny thinks he may be the last one. That is, until he miraculously finds Ellie, the only female mammoth left in the world. Their only problems: They can't stand each other--and Ellie somehow thinks she's a possum! Ellie comes with some excess baggage in the form of her two possum "brothers"-- Crash and Eddie, a couple of daredevil pranksters and cocky, loud-mouthed troublemakers. Manny, Sid and Diego quickly learn that the warming climate has one major drawback: A huge glacial dam holding off oceans of water is about to break, threatening the entire valley. The only chance of survival lies at the other end of the valley. So our three heroes, along with Ellie, Crash and Eddie, form the most unlikely family--in any "Age"-- as they embark on a mission across an ever-changing, increasingly dangerous landscape towards their salvation.
U | 1h 31min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 7 April 2006</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/i/Ice.Age.The.Meltdown.2006.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjAwODg3OTAxMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjg2NjYyMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDI1Mzc0MTIzOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzE2NjYyMw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,997_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ice Age 3: Dawn Of The Dinosaurs</title>
<summary>Storyline
After the events of "Ice Age: The Meltdown", life begins to change for Manny and his friends: Scrat is still on the hunt to hold onto his beloved acorn, while finding a possible romance in a female sabre-toothed squirrel named Scratte. Manny and Ellie, having since become an item, are expecting a baby, which leaves Manny anxious to ensure that everything is perfect for when his baby arrives. Diego is fed up with being treated like a house-cat and ponders the notion that he is becoming too laid-back. Sid begins to wish for a family of his own, and so steals some dinosaur eggs which leads to Sid ending up in a strange underground world where his herd must rescue him, while dodging dinosaurs and facing danger left and right, and meeting up with a one-eyed weasel known as Buck who hunts dinosaurs intently.
U | 1h 34min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 1 July 2009</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/i/Ice.Age.Dawn.Of.The.Dinosaurs.2009.720p.BrRip.RARBG.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BY2RkZWJmZjItYTUzNS00ZGI4LThjYTctYTdkOWZiODkxMjRhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTIzOTk5ODM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,694,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTYzNDg3ODQxMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTM1NTY0Mg@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ice Age 4: Continental Drift</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Scrat accidentally provokes a continental cataclysm with a storm, Manny is separated from Ellie and Peaches on an iceberg with Diego, Sid and Granny but he promises that he will find a way to return home. While crossing the ocean, they are captured by the cruel pirate Captain Gutt and his crew. However they escape and Manny plots a plan to steal Captain Gutt's ship and return to his homeland in a dangerous voyage through the sea. But the cruel pirates seek revenge against Manny and his family and friends.
U | 1h 28min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 13 July 2012</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/i/Ice.Age.Continental.Drift.2012.720p.BrRip.Ganool.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTM3NDM5MzY5Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjExMDUwOA@@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzUwODMxOTIxMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDYwMjg3OA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1729,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ice Age: Collision Course</title>
<summary>Storyline
Scrat's epic pursuit of his elusive acorn catapults him outside of Earth, where he accidentally sets off a series of cosmic events that transform and threaten the planet. To save themselves from peril, Manny, Sid, Diego, and the rest of the herd leave their home and embark on a quest full of thrills and spills, highs and lows, laughter and adventure while traveling to exotic new lands and encountering a host of colorful new characters.
U | 1h 34min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 1 July 2016</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/i/Ice.Age.Collision.Course.2016.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzFjYWM5NzgtMGIwMi00MmE3LWE3NTgtNmIwMmRkNmFmYzJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQ2MTMzODA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjQzNDQ0NTAyMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDk2MDc5OTE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,744_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Incredibles 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
While the Parr family has accepted its collective calling as superheroes, the fact remains that their special heroism is still illegal. After they are arrested after unsuccessfully trying to stop the Underminer, their future seems bleak. However, the wealthy Deavor siblings of Devtech offer new hope with a bold project to rehabilitate the public image and legal status of Supers, with Elastigirl being assigned on point to be the shining example. Now having agreed for now to stay at home to care of the kids, Mr. Incredible finds domestic life a daunting challenge, especially with baby Jack-Jack's newly emerged powers making him almost impossible to manage. However, Elastigirl soon has her own concerns dealing with the menace of a new supervillain, Screenslaver, who is wreaking havoc with his mind control abilities. Now, Elastigirl must solve the mystery of this enemy, who has malevolent designs on the world with the Parr family and friends key targets of this evil.
PG | 1h 58min | Animation , Action , Adventure | 13 July 2018</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Incredibles%202/Incredibles.2.2018.480p.Pahe.Film9.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Incredibles%202/Incredibles.2.2018.720p.MkvCage.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Incredibles%202/Incredibles.2.2018.1080p.MkvCage.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Incredibles%202/Incredibles.2.2018.1080p.Full.HD.Sector7.Film9.mkv(link 11 | 1080P FULL HD)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTEzNzY0OTg0NTdeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDU3OTg3MjUz._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc3NjMxMDI0Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzkwMDk1NDM@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,807_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Inside Out</title>
<summary>Storyline
Growing up can be a bumpy road, and it's no exception for Riley, who is uprooted from her Midwest life when her father starts a new job in San Francisco. Like all of us, Riley is guided by her emotions - Joy, Fear, Anger, Disgust and Sadness. The emotions live in Headquarters, the control center inside Riley's mind, where they help advise her through everyday life. As Riley and her emotions struggle to adjust to a new life in San Francisco, turmoil ensues in Headquarters. Although Joy, Riley's main and most important emotion, tries to keep things positive, the emotions conflict on how best to navigate a new city, house and school.
U | 1h 35min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 24 July 2015</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2015/Inside.Out.2015.720p.FardaDownload_ir.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2015/Inside.Out.2015.1080p.5.1CH.FardaDownload_ir.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOTgxMDQwMDk0OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjU5OTg2NDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTA0ODYwODcyMDBeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDUyODYzMDAx._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1556,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>James and the Giant Peach</title>
<summary>Storyline
James' happy life at the English seaside is rudely ended when his parents are killed by a rhinoceros and he goes to live with his two horrid aunts. Daringly saving the life of a spider he comes into possession of magic boiled crocodile tongues, after which an enormous peach starts to grow in the garden. Venturing inside he meets not only the spider but a number of new friends including a ladybug and a centipede who help him with his plan to try and get to New York.
U | 1h 19min | Animation, Adventure, Family | 2 August 1996</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/James%20and%20the%20Giant%20Peach%20%281996%29/James.And.The.Giant.Peach.1996.720p.BluRay.H264.AAC-RARBG.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTNkNWIwNGUtNTJlOC00NDU3LTk0NWEtNjNjNDM4NzRiNThkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTcwNDYxMjkwOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDI4OTEyNw@@._V1_SX1500_CR0,0,1500,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kangaroo Jack</title>
<summary>Storyline
Louis Booker and Charlie Carbone are close friends with an association with the mob. After the duo botch a delivery of stolen TVs, the duo are given a second chance by mob leader Sal Maggio, who happens to be Charlie's stepfather. The duo are to deliver $50,000 to a contact in Australia. As simple as the job sounds, complications emerge when a kangaroo steals the money. Now Charlie and Louis must find the kangaroo and get the money back before they find themselves in a worse predicament.
PG | 1h 29min | Action, Adventure, Comedy | 16 May 2003</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Hollywood/2003/Kangaroo%20Jack%20%282003%29/Kangaroo%20Jack.avi</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk1Njg5MjAyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNDAxMDg5._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTIxMDE0NTQxNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNjM4Mzc2._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kim Possible</title>
<summary>Everyday teen hero Kim Possible (Sadie Stanley) and her best friend Ron Stoppable (Sean Giambrone) embark on their freshman year of high school, all while saving the world from evil villains. While Kim and Ron have always been one step ahead of their opponents, navigating the social hierarchy of high school is more challenging than the action-heroes ever imagined. With Drakken (Todd Stashwick) and Shego (Taylor Ortega) lurking in the wings, Kim must rely on her family and friends on Team Possible -- Ron, tech-genius Wade (Issac Ryan Brown), new friend Athena (Ciara Wilson), and Rufus, a naked mole-rat -- to stop these super villains.
1h 26min | Action, Adventure, Comedy | TV Movie 15 February 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/k/Kim.Possible.2019.720p.WEB-DL.DM.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmJhMDIyMmYtOTY5ZS00YzViLTgyYzgtN2Q4Yjk2NDNkZWFmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjcwNTU1Mjk@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmJhMDIyMmYtOTY5ZS00YzViLTgyYzgtN2Q4Yjk2NDNkZWFmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjcwNTU1Mjk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kung Fu Panda</title>
<summary>Storyline
It's the story about a lazy, irreverent slacker panda, named Po, who is the biggest fan of Kung Fu around...which doesn't exactly come in handy while working every day in his family's noodle shop. Unexpectedly chosen to fulfill an ancient prophecy, Po's dreams become reality when he joins the world of Kung Fu and studies alongside his idols, the legendary Furious Five -- Tigress, Crane, Mantis, Viper and Monkey -- under the leadership of their guru, Master Shifu. But before they know it, the vengeful and treacherous snow leopard Tai Lung is headed their way, and it's up to Po to defend everyone from the oncoming threat. Can he turn his dreams of becoming a Kung Fu master into reality? Po puts his heart - and his girth - into the task, and the unlikely hero ultimately finds that his greatest weaknesses turn out to be his greatest strengths.
PG | 1h 32min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 4 July 2008</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/k/Kung.Fu.Panda.2008.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODJkZTZhMWItMDI3Yy00ZWZlLTk4NjQtOTI1ZjU5NjBjZTVjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODE5NzE3OTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,689,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDcxOTM0MDU2MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTIzMzA3NA@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,758_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kung Fu Panda 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
In the Valley of Peace, Po Ping is revelling in his fulfilled dreams as he serves as the fabled Dragon Warrior protecting his home with his heroes now his closest friends. However, Po and company learn that the murderous Lord Shen of Gongman City is threatening the land with a fearsome new weapon that could mean the end of kung fu. They attempt to stop him, but the panda is burdened with crippling memory flashbacks linked to this villain. Now with China in the balance, Po must learn about his past and find true inner peace against all opposition.
PG | 1h 30min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 10 June 2011</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/k/Kung.Fu.Panda.2.2011.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYzQ0ZWIxZjAtYWI3Yy00MGM0LWFjOGYtNzcyYThiOTA3ODI1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODE5NzE3OTE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTU2NTg3NDAwM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzUyNTIyNQ@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,754_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Kung Fu Panda 3</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Po's long-lost panda father suddenly reappears, the reunited duo travels to a secret panda paradise to meet scores of hilarious new panda characters. But when the supernatural villain Kai begins to sweep across China defeating all the kung fu masters, Po must do the impossible-learn to train a village full of his fun-loving, clumsy brethren to become the ultimate band of Kung Fu Pandas.
PG | 1h 35min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 11 March 2016</summary>
<link>http://dl.upload10.ir/Film/2016/Kung.Fu.Panda.3.2016.720p.FardaDownload_net.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUyNzgxNjg2M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTY1NDI1NjE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ0MTk3MTA4Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjE4OTY5NTE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,735_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>LEGO DC: Batman - Family Matters</title>
<summary>Storyline
In LEGO DC: Batman - Family Matters, suspicion is on high after Batman, Batgirl, Robin and other DC superheroes receive mysterious invitations. However, family values must remain strong when Batman and his team encounter the villainous Red Hood, who is obsessed with destroying the Bat-family and all of Gotham City.
1h 12min | Animation | 6 August 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl.roozdl.com/roozdl/1398/4/LEGO_DC_Batman_Family_Matters_2019_720p_WEB-DL.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDM1MWNiODQtNWM1NS00YjViLThlMGMtYjU2ZDk3MzU1OWJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTkwNDYxNzc@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/coN26fysHV5aTkzhYivZeeE5SuR.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Lego DC Comics Super Heroes: Aquaman - Rage of Atlantis</title>
<summary>Storyline
Aquaman must battle foes in the air, on land and in the depths of the Seven Seas, along with some help from The Justice League, to save the day .
1h 17min | Animation, Family | Video 31 July 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/l/Lego.Dc.Comics.Super.Heroes.Aquaman.Rage.Of.Atlantis.2018.720p.BrRip.RARBG.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzQyMjQ5YTUtNWY3Ni00NjZkLWExMmUtYTliYWRlNDIyZmJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDdmMjAzMWYtZTVhYy00ODU1LTgxNjEtYjU5Nzk3ZTBhZTBkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzU3NjUxMzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Lego DC Comics Super Heroes: The Flash</title>
<summary>Storyline
The morning sun shines on the jewel of the Metropolis skyline, The Daily Planet building. But when The Joker decides this building needs a renovation, it's time to sound the Trouble Alert because all bricks are about to break loose! The Justice League leaps into action but as the battle is brewing against The Joker something goes haywire with The Flash's powers causing him to get caught in a repeating time loop and even stranger is the yellow clad Reverse Flash taunting him at every turn! It will take all of Flash's speed, a little magic and the helping hands and paws of the Justice League's new recruits The Atom, Krypto the Super Dog and Ace the Bat Hound to break the cycle and save Metropolis!
U | 1h 18min | Animation, Action, Sci-Fi | Video 13 February 2018</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2018/Lego%20DC%20Comics%20Super%20Heroes-The%20Flash%20%282018%29/Lego.DC.Comics.Super.Heroes.The.Flash.2018.720p.WEB-DL.600MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODY5NjI2OTEtODI2ZC00MjJhLTk5MTEtNmM5MzlmNTUwNzEwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZmZjNjE4MzgtMmRmMS00ZTA0LWFlNWQtNThiOWZlYWE5NTY4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzI1NzMxNzM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Leo Da Vinci: Mission Mona Lisa</title>
<summary>Storyline
In the late Middle Age's Italy, Leonardo "Leo" Da Vinci is a young boy lover to invent advanced machines who lives happy with his best friend Lorenzo and beauty Lisa, being secretly fall in love with her. After to test the first dive suit of his creation in a lake, tragedy appears when coming back to home Lisa realizes that her house and lands have been burned by a fire. Owner of the lands threats Lisa's father to marry her with his son if he doesn't give all money he debts as retribution by the fire, causing Lisa's sorrow. Trying to save her, Leo Da Vinci decides travel to Florencia to gain money and pay the debt with help of Lorenzo. Unable to keep the secret, Lorenzo reveals Lisa Leo's plans, and Lisa joins her friends to make the travel to the big city, where they meet a storyteller that explains in a plaza the story of a pirate ship sunken with a great treasure inside it. Believing it as a true event, Leo buys the treasure map to the storyteller, but it's stolen by a rogue and orphan little child called Agnes. Making a deal with her, Leo recovers the map and Agnes joins the group at the same time that Niccol, a little child lover of science and astronomy who befriends with Lisa. All five arrive to Montecristo Island looking for the treasure, but not knowing that a pirates follow each step they make, waiting the right time to steal the treasure and eliminate Leo and his friends.
1h 25min | Animation, Adventure, Family | 11 January 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/l/Leo.Da.Vinci.Mission.Mona.Lisa.2018.720p.BrRip.DM.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjdkNjQ0MmMtZDFmZi00MTYxLWJkZmEtZDMyZDIxMzk3MTUwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg0ODQzNA@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTZkZDBhMzQtNzE2NS00NGE5LWE0ZjEtMGUwY2EwYmMzMmRhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODA1OTMzMTY@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,695_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Luis & the Aliens</title>
<summary>Storyline
"Luis" tells the story of an 11-year-old boy who makes friends with three lovable little aliens, who crash their spaceship at an abandon gas station near his house. In return for Luis' help in finding the home-shopping channel stuff they came for, they save Luis from boarding school - and an exciting adventure follows.
U | 1h 26min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 24 August 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/l/Luis.The.Aliens.2018.720p.BrRip.RARBG.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWQ1MTUwMWYtOTQ5OC00ZjRkLWIzNDUtODIwMDQ2NzI5MTZhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDg1NDcyMDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,709,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmEyZGIwMmQtNDRkNS00NGRhLThjZmUtNWYzMDE5YjMwMjE4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODUyMTk5MTY@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Minions</title>
<summary>Storyline
Ever since the dawn of time, the Minions have lived to serve the most despicable of masters. From the T-Rex to Napoleon, the easily distracted tribe has helped the biggest and the baddest of villains. Now, join protective leader Kevin, teenage rebel Stuart, and lovable little Bob on a global road trip. They'll earn a shot to work for a new boss, the world's first female supervillain, and try to save all of Minionkind from annihilation.
U | 1h 31min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 26 June 2015</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/m/Minions.2015.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg2MTMyMzU0M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTU3ODk4NTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjE4NjQzNjg5MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzQ1NDgwNjE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,960_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Missing Link</title>
<summary>Storyline
The charismatic Sir Lionel Frost considers himself to be the world's foremost investigator of myths and monsters. The trouble is none of his small-minded high-society peers seems to recognize this. Sir Lionel's last chance for acceptance by the adventuring elite rests on traveling to America's Pacific Northwest to prove the existence of a legendary creature. A living remnant of Man's primitive ancestry. The Missing Link.
PG | 1h 35min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 5 April 2019</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Missing.Link.2019.480p.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Missing.Link.2019.720p.MkvCage.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Missing.Link.2019.1080p.6CH.MkvCage.mkv(link 3 | 720P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWFmNWZmZWYtMWM3OC00YTYyLWIxNDMtOTRjNzhiYWQ0MDIwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODk2NDQ3MTA@._V1_SY999_CR0,0,672,999_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYxMjIzNjQ0NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzIzMjE3NjM@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,909_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Moana</title>
<summary>Storyline
Moana Waialiki is a sea voyaging enthusiast and the only daughter of a chief in a long line of navigators. When her island's fishermen can't catch any fish and the crops fail, she learns that the demigod Maui caused the blight by stealing the heart of the goddess, Te Fiti. The only way to heal the island is to persuade Maui to return Te Fiti's heart, so Moana sets off on an epic journey across the Pacific. The film is based on stories from Polynesian mythology.
PG | 1h 47min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 2 December 2016</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://dl.upload10.ir/Film/2016/Moana/Moana.2016.720p.ShAaNiG.FardaDownload.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://dl.upload10.ir/Film/2016/Moana/Moana.2016.1080p.6CH.ShAaNiG.FardaDownload.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjI4MzU5NTExNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzY1MTEwMDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ5YzVlOTctYjA0MS00YWJjLThkOTMtYTg3MzQ1YTY3YzY1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzExMzk5MTQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Monster Family</title>
<summary>Storyline
Despite the title, the Wishbone family are far from happy. In an attempt to reconnect as a family, Mum and Emma plan a fun night out. However, her plan backfires when an evil witch curses them, and they're all turned into Monsters.
PG | 1h 33min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 2 March 2018</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/Monster%20Family%20%282017%29/Monster.Family.720p.BRRip.850MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjIzNzUxMjMzNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzg0MTY2NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,699,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjg2Y2IwMzQtNTJhMi00MzU3LWJjNWYtM2M5NzViNWI3MGM2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjQyMDM3NA@@._V1_SX1414_CR0,0,1414,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Monster Island</title>
<summary>Storyline
When young Lucas finds out he's not really a human; the news changes his whole world. Especially since his first monster transformation happened in front of the most popular kids at school!
PG | 1h 20min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 21 July 2017</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/Monster%20Island%20%282017%29/Monster.Island.2017.720.WEB-DL.650MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWIxZjQ2ZDQtZGIyNy00MjUyLWFjYTMtNTYzZGQxNTA5NjgzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjgzNjA3Mw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,706,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2U5MjdiODktYmQ1Mi00ZGU2LTllNDgtM2E2Mzc3Mzc2MjZmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjgzNjA3Mw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Mulan</title>
<summary>Storyline
This retelling of the old Chinese folktale is about the story of a young Chinese maiden who learns that her weakened and lame father is to be called up into the army in order to fight the invading Huns. Knowing that he would never survive the rigours of war in his state, she decides to disguise herself and join in his place. Unknown to her, her ancestors are aware of this and to prevent it, they order a tiny disgraced dragon, Mushu to join her in order to force her to abandon her plan. He agrees, but when he meets Mulan, he learns that she cannot be dissuaded and so decides to help her in the perilous times ahead.
1h 28min | Animation, Adventure, Family | 16 October 1998</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/Mulan%20%281998%29/Mulan.1998.720p.BRrip.x264.GAZ.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODkxNGQ1NWYtNzg0Ny00Yjg3LThmZTItMjE2YjhmZTQ0ODY5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,673,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOGJmYzEyNmYtN2ZlMy00ZDRiLWJiZGEtMzU1ZmNjYzE2MGIwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjkzNjUzODY@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>My Little Pony: The Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
After a dark force conquers Canterlot, the Mane 6 - Twilight Sparkle, Applejack, Rainbow Dash, Pinkie Pie, Fluttershy, and Rarity - embark on an unforgettable journey beyond Equestria where they meet new friends and exciting challenges on a quest to use the magic of friendship to save their homeland.
U | 1h 39min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 20 October 2017</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/My%20Little%20Pony-The%20Movie%20%282017%29/My.Little.Pony.The.Movie.2017.720p.HDRip.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMmMxNWNhNjItZjhmMC00ZmViLThlYjItZDk5YTQ1MWZkOGM1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzY2ODYzOTU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,657,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTMxMWFlMWItM2NlNi00MmExLTk3NGUtM2VlYzY2YmJmMzQwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzY2ODYzOTU@._V1_SY1000_SX1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Norm of the North: Keys to the Kingdom</title>
<summary>Storyline
Norm, the newly crowned polar bear king of the arctic, must save New York City and his home. But Norm goes from hero to villain when he's framed for a crime he didn't commit. He must work with his friends to clear his good name and help save his kingdom in a winner-take-all hockey match.
PG | 1h 31min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 31 August 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/n/Norm.Of.The.North.Keys.To.The.Kingdom.2018.720p.WEB-DL.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWE1MmNmMTItZGRiNi00N2E3LTk5YTEtMmQxMDQ5YTM2OTk2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTg4MDYyNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjUwOGM1MTktNmUwOS00YmNkLTgxZDktZTFiYjI0MTcwMjZmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTg4MDYyNw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Paddington</title>
<summary>Storyline
A young Peruvian bear with a passion for all things British travels to London in search of a home. Finding himself lost and alone at Paddington Station, he begins to realize that city life is not all he had imagined - until he meets the kind Brown family, who read the label around his neck ('Please look after this bear. Thank you.') and offer him a temporary haven. It looks as though his luck has changed until this rarest of bears catches the eye of a museum taxidermist.
PG | 1h 35min | Adventure, Comedy, Family | 28 November 2014</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Hollywood/2014/Paddington%20%282014%29/Paddington.2014.1080p.BluRay.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTAxOTMwOTkwNDZeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDEyMTI1NjMx._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjEzNDU0MTk4Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDc2MTEwNDE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,744_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Paddington 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
Paddington is happily settled with the Brown family in Windsor Gardens, where he has become a popular member of the community, spreading joy and marmalade wherever he goes. While searching for the perfect present for his beloved Aunt Lucy's 100th birthday, Paddington spots a unique pop-up book in Mr. Gruber's antique shop, and embarks upon a series of odd jobs to buy it. But when the book is stolen, it's up to Paddington and the Browns to unmask the thief.
PG | 1h 43min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 10 November 2017</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/p/Paddington.2.2017.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMmYwNWZlNzEtNjE4Zi00NzQ4LWI2YmUtOWZhNzZhZDYyNmVmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzYzODM3Mzg@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDhiODMxMGMtOWQ5Ni00NWViLTg5ODUtNTI4MmM4YzNhMGJiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTk1MzcwNTI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Peter Rabbit </title>
<summary>Storyline
Based on the books by Beatrix Potter: Peter Rabbit (James Corden;) his three sisters: Flopsy (Margot Robbie,) Mopsy (Elizabeth Debicki) and Cotton Tail (Daisy Ridley) and their cousin Benjamin (Colin Moody) enjoy their days harassing Mr McGregor in his vegetable garden. Until one day he dies and no one can stop them roaming across his house and lands for a full day or so. However, when one of Mr McGregor's relatives inherits the house and goes to check it out, he finds much more than he bargained for. What ensues, is a battle of wills between the new Mr McGregor and the rabbits. But when he starts to fall in love with Bea (Rose Byrne,) a real lover of all nature, his feelings towards them begin to change. But is it too late?
PG | 1h 35min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 16 March 2018</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2018/Peter.Rabbit.2018.480p.PaHe.Film9.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2018/Peter.Rabbit.2018.720p.MkvCage.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2018/Peter.Rabbit.2018.1080p.6CH.MkvCage.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOWE4YzE3Y2MtYzIyZS00NjA4LTliMDgtY2U0NGM2NzI4MjZlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTU5Mzk0NjE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOTM1Njc4NDM2M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODk2NTI2MzI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ploey You Never Fly Alone</title>
<summary>Storyline
A plover chick has not learned to fly when his family migrates in the fall. He must survive the arctic winter, vicious enemies and himself in order to be reunited with his beloved one next spring.</summary>
U | 1h 23min | Animation, Adventure, Family | 6 July 2018
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/p/Ploe.You.Never.Fly.Alone.2017.720p.BrRip.F2M.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTQ0MjgxZmItNGQ2Ni00NDMxLTg3ZWMtZDQ5ZjE0YTc3ZDE5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjgxNDgzOA@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOGEzNWRmMjYtZTU2ZS00YTRjLTk1ZjgtZDEwNGVjMDI5N2Y2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjgxNDgzOA@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,756_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Pokmon Detective Pikachu</title>
<summary>Storyline
The story begins when ace detective Harry Goodman goes mysteriously missing, prompting his 21-year-old son Tim to find out what happened. Aiding in the investigation is Harry's former Pokmon partner, Detective Pikachu: a hilariously wise-cracking, adorable super-sleuth who is a puzzlement even to himself. Finding that they are uniquely equipped to communicate with one another, Tim and Pikachu join forces on a thrilling adventure to unravel the tangled mystery. Chasing clues together through the neon-lit streets of Ryme City--a sprawling, modern metropolis where humans and Pokmon live side by side in a hyper-realistic live-action world--they encounter a diverse cast of Pokmon characters and uncover a shocking plot that could destroy this peaceful co-existence and threaten the whole Pokmon universe.
PG | 1h 44min | Action, Adventure, Comedy | 10 May 2019</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Pokemon.Detective.Pikachu.2019.480p.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Pokemon.Detective.Pikachu.2019.720p.MkvCage.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Pokemon.Detective.Pikachu.2019.1080p.6CH.MkvCage.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDU4Mzc3NzE5NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzE1NzI1NzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTNmOGE1ZmQtYjZmYy00MDhkLThkZjYtNzkyZDYxNTA5ZTE0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg2NjQwMDQ@._V1_SY739_CR0,0,1776,739_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Pokmon the Movie: The Power of Us</title>
<summary>Storyline
Every year the citizens of Fura City celebrate a Wind Festival. Where people live together with the wind. Long Ago, on the final day of the festival the Legendary Pokemon Lugia and bestow the blessings of the wind upon the people. This Film Focuses on Everyone's Story. from Lisa, a high school girl who is just starting out as a Pokemon trainer, to Karachi, a guy who can't stop lying to Torito, a researcher who lacks confidence in himself, to Hisui, an old lady who hates touching Pokemon, and Rarugo, a mysterious young girl who watches over the forest by herself.
PG | 1h 37min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 24 November 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/p/Pokemon.The.Movie.The.Power.Of.Us.2018.720p.BrRip.Ganool.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzM2NzM2NmMtNjZlNi00YTcyLWIwYmUtYmE1MWVmYTNiODRlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDkzMjE0NDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTY5MGZiNDctOWRjNi00N2VmLWIwMDUtYjZiYzMzYzZiODI5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzEyMDQ1MDA@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Power Rangers</title>
<summary>Storyline
High school outcasts stumble upon an old alien ship, where they acquire superpowers and are dubbed the Power Rangers. Learning that an old enemy of the previous generation has returned to exact vengeance, the group must harness their powers and use them to work together and save the world.
12A | 2h 4min | Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi | 23 March 2017</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Hollywood/2017/Power%20Rangers%20%282017%29/Power.Rangers.2017.1080p.BRRip.6CH.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU1MTkxNzc5NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTM2Mzk3MTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,648,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWYwMWNkYWQtZGM0NS00ZDFkLThkYzctOTkyN2UwZDk4Zjk3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjUwNzk3NDc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ralph Breaks the Internet</title>
<summary>Storyline
Taking place six years after saving the arcade from Turbo's vengeance, the Sugar Rush arcade cabinet has broken, forcing Ralph and Vanellope to travel to the Internet via the newly-installed Wi-Fi router in Litwak's Arcade to retrieve the piece capable of saving the game.
PG | 1h 52min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 30 November 2018</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Ralph.Breaks.the.Internet.2018.480p.Farsi.Dub.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Ralph.Breaks.the.Internet.2018.720p.Farsi.Dub.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Ralph.Breaks.the.Internet.2018.1080p.Farsi.Dub.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgwMDA0Mzg4OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjk1MjQ2NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjU0YWE2NjItZTdlZi00ZjhlLWEzOGMtMTUxYjllOTkyMmYwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzc1MTQ5MTI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,712_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ratatouille</title>
<summary>Storyline
A rat named Remy dreams of becoming a great French chef despite his family's wishes and the obvious problem of being a rat in a decidedly rodent-phobic profession. When fate places Remy in the sewers of Paris, he finds himself ideally situated beneath a restaurant made famous by his culinary hero, Auguste Gusteau. Despite the apparent dangers of being an unlikely - and certainly unwanted - visitor in the kitchen of a fine French restaurant, Remy's passion for cooking soon sets into motion a hilarious and exciting rat race that turns the culinary world of Paris upside down.
PG | 1h 51min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 12 October 2007</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2007/Ratatouille.2007.480p.Farsi.Dubbed.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Ratatouille.2007.Farsi.Dubbed.720p.YIFY.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Ratatouille.2007.Farsi.Dubbed.1080p.YIFY.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTMzODU0NTkxMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjQ4MzMzMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTYzMDg4NzA0MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzM4MzMzMw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,786_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Rise of The Guardians</title>
<summary>Storyline
When an evil spirit known as Pitch lays down the gauntlet to take over the world, the immortal Guardians must join forces for the first time to protect the hopes, beliefs, and imaginations of children all over the world.
PG | 1h 37min | Animation, Adventure, Family | 30 November 2012</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2012/Rise.of.the.Guardians.2012.480p.2Dooble.Farsi.Dubbed.Film9.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2012/Rise.of.the.Guardians.2012.720p.ShAaNiG.2Dooble.Farsi.Dubbed.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2012/Rise.of.the.Guardians.2012.1080p.ShAaNiG.2Dooble.Farsi.Dubbed.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTkzMjgwMDg1M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTgzNTI1OA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,643,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMGEyZDNmODItMGEzNC00ZTM2LWEyZWUtMDlhNzYwY2UxMmEyL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzEyNjA4Mzg@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Santa's Little Helpers</title>
<summary>Storyline
Fan favorites - the Minions - are back for another adventure. Having been accidently dropped off at the North Pole, our Minion pals make the most of the situation by trying to become elves.
4min | Animation, Short, Comedy | Video 5 February 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/s/Santas.Little.Helpers.2019.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7lPl9jxnLyqSgxxvDUDCj601ex8.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7jzVimxqmwiYjp6cfxEqJ9yPvko.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Scooby-Doo! and the Curse of the 13th Ghost</title>
<summary>Storyline
Scooby-Doo and the gang must track down the last of thirteen ghosts they had hunted years ago.
Animation, Action, Adventure | TV Movie 5 February 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/s/Scooby.Doo.And.The.Curse.Of.The.13th.Ghost.2019.1080p.WEB-DL.CMRG.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzYzYThmMGQtOTk2Ny00OGU2LWFiOTItNTAwOTYxMDA5YjAzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTQ1Mzg0Mzg@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,721,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzYzYThmMGQtOTk2Ny00OGU2LWFiOTItNTAwOTYxMDA5YjAzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTQ1Mzg0Mzg@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,721,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Sgt. Stubby: An American Hero</title>
<summary>Storyline
With the war to end all wars looming, a young army "doughboy" Robert Conroy has his life forever changed when a little dog with a stubby tail wanders into camp as the men of the 102nd Infantry Regiment train on the grounds of Yale University. Conroy gives his new friend a name, a family, and a chance to embark on the adventure that would define a century. Despite lacking formal military working dog training, Stubby the dog and his human companions find themselves in the trenches of France and on the path to history. French Infantryman Gaston Baptiste befriends the duo and accompanies them along their epic journey through harsh conditions and incredible acts of courage. For his valorous actions, Stubby is recognized as the first canine ever promoted to the rank of Sergeant in U.S. Army history.
PG | 1h 24min | Animation, Adventure, Family | 10 August 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/s/Sgt.Stubby.An.American.Hero.2018.720p.WEB-DL.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY5NzEwNDczMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjY1MTY4NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,678,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWVlMGQzZGUtZTNlYi00YzNhLTkyZDgtNzgzNGRmNjc2ZTQ3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTU5Mzk0NjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Shark Tale</title>
<summary>Storyline
The sea underworld is shaken up when the son of the shark mob boss is found dead and a young fish named Oscar is found at the scene. Being a bottom feeder, Oscar takes advantage of the situation and makes himself look like he killed the finned mobster. Oscar soon comes to realize that his claim may have serious consequences.
U | 1h 30min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 15 October 2004</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2004/Shark%20Tale%20%282004%29/Shark%20Tale%20%282004%29.avi</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTMxMjY0NzE2M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTc3ODcyMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,677,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjIyMjcwNzc1M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODI4ODcyMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1659,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Sherlock Gnomes </title>
<summary>Storyline
Garden gnomes, Gnomeo & Juliet, recruit renowned detective Sherlock Gnomes to investigate the mysterious disappearance of other garden ornaments.
U | 1h 26min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 11 May 2018</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2018/Sherlock%20Gnomes%20%282018%29/Sherlock.Gnomes.2018.720p.BRRip.MkvCage.WS.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk4NzU3NzU2NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDc4NTI3NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,640,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2RhOTI1YjktOGYwMS00MDdkLTg0MWYtNGIxNmRkMWM4NDI5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODEyMzI2OTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Shrek</title>
<summary>Storyline
When a green ogre named Shrek discovers his swamp has been 'swamped' with all sorts of fairytale creatures by the scheming Lord Farquaad, Shrek sets out with a very loud donkey by his side to 'persuade' Farquaad to give Shrek his swamp back. Instead, a deal is made. Farquaad, who wants to become the King, sends Shrek to rescue Princess Fiona, who is awaiting her true love in a tower guarded by a fire-breathing dragon. But once they head back with Fiona, it starts to become apparent that not only does Shrek, an ugly ogre, begin to fall in love with the lovely princess, but Fiona is also hiding a huge secret.
U | 1h 30min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 29 June 2001</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2001/Shrek%20%282001%29/Shrek%20%5B2001%5D.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOGZhM2FhNTItODAzNi00YjA0LWEyN2UtNjJlYWQzYzU1MDg5L2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,671,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTAyODc3Njc1NjdeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU3MDQ3MDgyNDY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1659,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Shrek 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
Shrek has rescued Princess Fiona, got married, and now is time to meet the parents. Shrek, Fiona, and Donkey set off to Far, Far Away to meet Fiona's mother and father. But not everyone is happy. Shrek and the King find it hard to get along, and there's tension in the marriage. It's not just the family who are unhappy. Prince Charming returns from a failed attempt at rescuing Fiona, and works alongside his mother, the Fairy Godmother, to try and find a way to get Shrek away from Fiona.
U | 1h 33min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 2 July 2004</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2004/Shrek%202%20%282004%29/Shrek%202%202004.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMDJhMGRjN2QtNDUxYy00NGM3LThjNGQtMmZiZTRhNjM4YzUxL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SY1000_SX677_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZjM1YzE1ZTgtMmUxNy00ZGU2LWE0OTYtMjA1Nzg4NmU0MGE4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMwODY0MTg@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Shrek The Third</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Fiona's father and King of Far Far Away passes away, the clumsy Shrek becomes the immediate successor of the throne. However, Shrek decides to find the legitimate heir Artie in a distant kingdom with his friends Donkey and Puss in Boots to be able return to his beloved house in the swamp with the pregnant Fiona. Meanwhile, the envious and ambitious Prince Charming joins the villains of the fairytales plotting a coup d'tat to become the new king.
U | 1h 33min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 29 June 2007</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2007/Shrek%20the%20Third%20%282007%29/ShrekTheThird%20%5B2007%5D.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOTgyMjc3ODk2MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjY0MjEzMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNTI1MDg0ODEyOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDQzNDYyMw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Shrek Forever After</title>
<summary>Storyline
The once hideous ogre Shrek is now living a good life with wife Fiona and his three children. But he soon has a meltdown in front of them and his friends during his kids' birthday party. He suddenly wants to be a real ogre like he was before he ever met Fiona. So he turns to devious deal maker Rumplestiltskin for help. At first, Shrek lives the life he once lost and everything is good. But he soon finds out that he has been set up by Rumplestiltskin, who now rules the land with an iron fist. Teaming with friends Donkey, Fiona and Puss in Boots, Shrek is in for the fight of his life as he tries to get his life back before time runs out.
U | 1h 33min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 2 July 2010</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2010/Shrek%20Forever%20After%20%282010%29/Shrek.4.2010.720p.BluRay.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA4MDQwMDk5Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTY4MDQ1Mw@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg3MDI4MTk2MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDE2NjY0Mw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,754_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Sing</title>
<summary>Storyline
In a town with no humans, just animals, a koala named Buster Moon realizes he will soon lose his theater if he cannot turn his luck around. He comes up with a plan to host a singing competition, where the winner will receive $1,000. Will this be enough to return his theater to glory?
U | 1h 48min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 27 January 2017</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/s/Sing.2016.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTYzODYzODU2Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTc1MTA2NzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYzI2MDdiMGEtMjZjOS00M2YyLTg5MjItMjkzNzBjZTQ2MDFiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzMyODMwMTI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Smallfoot</title>
<summary>Storyline
A yeti named Migo is convinced that a human known only as "Small Foot" is real and has to prove to his tribe that it does exist with the help of Meechee and the S.E.S - Smallfoot Evidentiary Society.
PG | 1h 36min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 12 October 2018</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Smallfoot.2018.480p.Pahe.Film9.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Smallfoot.2018.720p.MkvCage.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2018/Smallfoot.2018.1080p.MkvCage.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTVkYTZlZWItZTc0ZS00MTIzLThlNjItNmNkNDA5YzIwZGZjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODQzNTE3ODc@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjU5ZDVkODUtYWM5YS00NjI1LTg3MmQtNDQ2MGEwOWIxMzY3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzEwODIxNzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Smurfs: The Lost Village</title>
<summary>Storyline
In this fully animated, all-new take on the Smurfs, a mysterious map sets Smurfette and her best friends Brainy, Clumsy and Hefty on an exciting and thrilling race through the Forbidden Forest filled with magical creatures to find a mysterious lost village before the evil wizard Gargamel does. Embarking on a roller-coaster journey full of action and danger, the Smurfs are on a course that leads to the discovery of the biggest secret in Smurf history!
U | 1h 30min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 31 March 2017</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/Smurfs-The%20Lost%20Village%20%282017%29/Smurfs.The.Lost.Village.2017.720p.BRRip.800MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg1NjgyMTYzM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzIxNDc4MDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjEyNDc4NzA0MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzE5NzAwODE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,960_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</title>
<summary>Storyline
Miles Morales comes across the long-dead Peter Parker. This Peter Parker is not from his world though; he's from somewhere else in the multiverse. With Parker's guidance, Miles will become Spider-Man: and through that he will become part of the ever-expanding 'Spider-Verse'.
PG | 1h 57min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 12 December 2018</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/s/Spider.Man.Into.The.Spider.Verse.2018.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv(link 1 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/s/Spider.Man.Into.The.Spider.Verse.2018.1080p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv(link 2 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMzMzQ0NzI5Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjc2NTY0NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDY0NTNlMTYtYjAwNS00NmU0LWJjMGQtMDU2NmUxMjk4YjBiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODUxOTgwNDg@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Storks</title>
<summary>Storyline
Storks deliver babies...or at least they used to. Now they deliver packages for global internet giant Cornerstore.com. Junior, the company's top delivery stork, is about to be promoted when he accidentally activates the Baby Making Machine, producing an adorable and wholly unauthorized baby girl. Desperate to deliver this bundle of trouble before the boss gets wise, Junior and his friend Tulip, the only human on Stork Mountain, race to make their first-ever baby drop - in a wild and revealing journey that could make more than one family whole and restore the storks' true mission in the world.
U | 1h 27min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 14 October 2016</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/s/Storks.2016.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTYxNjI3MzcwMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTIyNDY5OTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDE5ZmRkZTEtMzEzYi00ZWQ2LWIxZTUtN2RkZDI0MjkxNTllXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQxNjcxNQ@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,747_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Tangled</title>
<summary>Storyline
After receiving the healing powers from a magical flower, the baby Princess Rapunzel is kidnapped from the palace in the middle of the night by Mother Gothel. Mother Gothel knows that the flower's magical powers are now growing within the golden hair of Rapunzel, and to stay young, she must lock Rapunzel in her hidden tower. Rapunzel is now a teenager and her hair has grown to a length of 70-feet. The beautiful Rapunzel has been in the tower her entire life, and she is curious of the outside world. One day, the bandit Flynn Ryder scales the tower and is taken captive by Rapunzel. Rapunzel strikes a deal with the charming thief to act as her guide to travel to the place where the floating lights come from that she has seen every year on her birthday. Rapunzel is about to have the most exciting and magnificent journey of her life.
PG | 1h 40min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 28 January 2011</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2010/Tangled%20%282010%29/Tangled.2010.720p.x264.Br.YIFY.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTAxNDYxMjg0MjNeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU3MDcyNTk2OTM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTFmYjE5MGQtZGJhZC00ZGY1LThiODEtMWY1OGRlNWE3ZWMyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQzMDM1MDY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1397,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Teen Titans Go! To the Movies (2018)</title>
<summary>Storyline
It seems to the Teens that all the major superheroes out there are starring in their own movies-everyone but the Teen Titans, that is. But de facto leader Robin is determined to remedy the situation, and be seen as a star instead of a sidekick. If only they could get the hottest Hollywood film director to notice them. With a few madcap ideas and a song in their heart, the Teen Titans head to Tinsel Town, certain to pull off their dream. But when the group is radically misdirected by a seriously super villain and his maniacal plan to take over the Earth, things really go awry. The team finds their friendship and their fighting spirit failing, putting the very fate of the Teen Titans themselves on the line.
PG | 1h 24min | Animation , Action , Comedy | 3 August 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/Teen.Titans.Go.To.The.Movies.2018.720p.BrRip.RARBG.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjM3NDMwMDE2N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDQ1Mjg5NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,684,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTkxMGI1YzYtMmI4Ni00ZGNjLTg0MjYtYzE2NDYyMjFhZTVkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjQ4NjY2MzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Adventures of Tintin: The Secret of the Unicorn</title>
<summary>Storyline
Having bought a model ship, the Unicorn, for a pound off a market stall Tintin is initially puzzled that the sinister Mr. Sakharine should be so eager to buy it from him, resorting to murder and kidnapping Tintin - accompanied by his marvellous dog Snowy - to join him and his gang as they sail to Morocco on an old cargo ship. Sakharine has bribed the crew to revolt against the ship's master, drunken Captain Haddock, but Tintin, Snowy and Haddock escape, arriving in Morocco at the court of a sheikh, who also has a model of the Unicorn. Haddock tells Tintin that over three hundred years earlier his ancestor Sir Francis Haddock was forced to scuttle the original Unicorn when attacked by a piratical forebear of Sakharine but he managed to save his treasure and provide clues to its location in three separate scrolls, all of which were secreted in models of the Unicorn. Tintin and Sakharine have one each and the villain intends to use the glass-shattering top Cs of operatic soprano the Milanese Nightingale to secure the third. With aid from bumbling Interpol agents the Thompson Twins our boy hero, his dog and the captain must prevent Sakharine from obtaining all three scrolls to fulfil the prophesy that only the last of the Haddocks can discover the treasure's whereabouts.
PG | 1h 47min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 26 October 2011</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2011/The.Adventures.of.Tintin.2011.480p.Farsi.Dubbed.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2011/The.Adventures.of.Tintin.2011.720p.Farsi.Dubbed.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2011/The.Adventures.of.Tintin.2011.1080p.Farsi.Dubbed.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDE5MDExNTQ1OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDIxMTM5Ng@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTM0ODIzMTA5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzk2MjQxNw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Angry Birds Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
In the 3D animated comedy, The Angry Birds Movie, we'll finally find out why the birds are so angry. The movie takes us to an island populated entirely by happy, flightless birds - or almost entirely. In this paradise, Red (Jason Sudeikis, We're the Millers, Horrible Bosses), a bird with a temper problem, speedy Chuck (Josh Gad in his first animated role since Frozen), and the volatile Bomb (Danny McBride, This is the End, Eastbound and Down) have always been outsiders. But when the island is visited by mysterious green piggies, it's up to these unlikely outcasts to figure out what the pigs are up to. Featuring a hilarious, all-star voice cast that includes Bill Hader (Trainwreck, Inside Out), Maya Rudolph (Bridesmaids, Sisters), and Peter Dinklage (Game of Thrones), as well as Kate McKinnon (Saturday Night Live, Ghostbusters), Keegan-Michael Key (Key & Peele), Tony Hale (Veep, Arrested Development), Tituss Burgess (Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt), Ike Barinholtz (Neighbors, Sisters), Hannibal Buress (Daddy's Home, Broad City), Jillian Bell (22 Jump Street), Danielle Brooks (Orange is the New Black), Latin music sensation Romeo Santos, YouTube stars Smosh (Ian Hecox and Anthony Padilla), and country music superstar Blake Shelton, who writes and preforms the original song "Friends," the Columbia Pictures/Rovio Entertainment film is directed by Fergal Reilly and Clay Kaytis and produced by John Cohen and Catherine Winder. The screenplay is by Jon Vitti, and the film is executive produced by Mikael Hed and David Maisel.
U | 1h 37min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 13 May 2016</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/a/Angry.Birds.2016.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3MjU0NDA0OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTc0MTU3OTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,702,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzNmMTFlMmItMzhiNS00YzcxLTkwZjEtNDQ4NWRlZDFhMjQzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzg1MDQ1NzA@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The BFG</title>
<summary>Storyline
Sophie is snatched from her orphanage early one morning by the B.F.G. (Big Friendly Giant), whom she witnesses engaged in mysterious activities, and whisked away to Giant Country. She is soon put at ease, as she learns that B.F.G.'s job is to collect, catalogue and deliver pleasant dreams to children. She joins him that night, but the mean giants follow them, planning to eat the children. Sophie enlists the help of the Queen, by making up a dream for her, and with the backing of the armed forces, they defeat the mean giants.
U | 1h 27min | Animation, Adventure, Drama | 5 November 1987</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/The%20BFG%20%281989%29/The.BFG.1989.720p.BRRip.800MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk4OTgwNDA3MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjAyMjAwNDE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYTRlODAzMDUtZTBhNi00ZjY1LTk2M2MtNGRlZDEwNDYyYmRlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjUwNzk3NDc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The B.F.G</title>
<summary>Storyline
Ten-year-old Sophie is in for the adventure of a lifetime when she meets the Big Friendly Giant. Naturally scared at first, the young girl soon realizes that the 24-foot behemoth is actually quite gentle and charming. As their friendship grows, Sophie's presence attracts the unwanted attention of Bloodbottler, Fleshlumpeater and other giants. After traveling to London, Sophie and the BFG must convince Queen Elizabeth to help them get rid of all the bad giants once and for all.
PG | 1h 57min | Adventure, Family, Fantasy | 22 July 2016</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Bfg.2016.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjAzOTUzNTY3Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjYwNzE5ODE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzgzMGYxNmMtNWJiMy00ZmNjLTgxNmYtNThlYTY2ZDM0M2QyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzg0NTE4MDQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Boss Baby</title>
<summary>Storyline
Seven-year-old Tim Templeton has always had an overactive imagination--and for the past seven years--life has been all peaches for him, getting all the love and affection from his caring parents. However, after the arrival of Boss Baby, an unexpected new brother dressed in a black suit complete with a tie and a briefcase, Tim won't be the centre of attention anymore, as the powerful sibling takes over the whole house, robbing him of all care, little by little. But, soon, Tim and the new Boss in a diaper will need to put differences aside and join forces, as a sneaky scheme involving the head of Puppy Co. threatens to tilt the balance of power towards their insidiously adorable furry antagonists, not to mention that the next Pet Convention is only in two days. Brothers, hurry up.
U | 1h 37min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 1 April 2017</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Boss.Baby.2017.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5MzUxNzgxNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTM2NzQ3MjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,685,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMGYwYzM4MzEtNzIyZS00NzIwLWFmNTEtYzdjYjE5NmFkMjA1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjUyNDk2ODc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Christmas Chronicles</title>
<summary>Storyline
The story of sister and brother, Kate and Teddy Pierce, whose Christmas Eve plan to catch Santa Claus on camera turns into an unexpected journey that most kids could only dream about.
1h 44min | Adventure , Comedy , Family | 22 November 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Christmas.Chronicles.2018.720p.WEB-DL.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTA3NjU3OTM2MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjQ2MzE1NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGEyMjcwMWMtYThmYi00ZDJkLTljYTItYzFjNmIxZDQ2N2FkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTExODIyNDM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Croods</title>
<summary>Storyline
"The Croods" are an eccentric family of cavemen, who survive the harsh terrain by living accordingly to a strict set of rules. But when their home is destroyed in the wake of an impending disaster known as "The End", they are forced to leave their home of shelter and security, and into the wilderness of the unknown to find a new home.
U | 1h 38min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 22 March 2013</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2013/The.Croods.2013.480p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film2Media.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2013/The.Croods.2013.720p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film2Media.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2013/The.Croods.2013.1080p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film2Media.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTcyOTc2OTA1Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTI1MjkzOQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTNiMjdkMTEtYzUwMi00YTk0LWJlYWMtYmY3N2ViMDExMDM5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTc5MDI5NjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Emperors New Groove</title>
<summary>Storyline
In this animated comedy from the folks at Disney, the vain and cocky Emperor Kuzco is a very busy man. Besides maintaining his "groove", and firing his suspicious administrator, Yzma; he's also planning to build a new waterpark just for himself for his birthday. However, this means destroying one of the villages in his kingdom. Meanwhile, Yzma is hatching a plan to get revenge and usurp the throne. But, in a botched assassination courtesy of Yzma's right-hand man, Kronk, Kuzco is magically transformed into a llama. Now, Kuzco finds himself the property of Pacha, a lowly llama herder whose home is ground zero for the water park. Upon discovering the llama's true self, Pacha offers to help resolve the Emperor's problem and regain his throne, only if he promises to move his water park.
U | 1h 18min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 16 February 2001</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/The%20Emperor%27s%20New%20Groove%20%282000%29/The.Emperors.New.Groove.2000.720p.BluRay.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZGQwNmFhNjctNzQ0Yy00ZmE5LWIyMTEtYTZhZWQ4OTFmNDI2L2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTMxMjgxMzA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ4NzE1OTkxN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDkxOTAyNw@@._V1_SX1684_CR0,0,1684,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Emoji Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
The Emoji Movie unlocks the never-before-seen secret world inside your smartphone. Hidden within the messaging app is Textopolis, a bustling city where all your favorite emojis live, hoping to be selected by the phone's user. In this world, each emoji has only one facial expression - except for Gene, an exuberant emoji who was born without a filter and is bursting with multiple expressions. Determined to become "normal" like the other emojis, Gene enlists the help of his handy best friend Hi-5 and the notorious code breaker emoji Jailbreak. Together, they embark on an epic "app-venture" through the apps on the phone, each its own wild and fun world, to find the Code that will fix Gene. But when a greater danger threatens the phone, the fate of all emojis depends on these three unlikely friends who must save their world before it's deleted forever.
U | 1h 26min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 4 August 2017</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/The%20Emoji%20Movie%20%282017%29/The.Emoji.Movie.2017.720p.BRRip.850MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTkzMzM3OTM2Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDM0NDU3MjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjMxNTYwOTIzMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzMxNTMzMjI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,744_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Good Dinosaur</title>
<summary>Storyline
"The Good Dinosaur" asks the question: What if the asteroid that forever changed life on Earth missed the planet completely and giant dinosaurs never became extinct? In this epic journey into the world of dinosaurs, an Apatosaurus named Arlo makes an unlikely human friend. While travelling through a harsh and mysterious landscape, Arlo learns the power of confronting his fears and discovers what he is truly capable of.
PG | 1h 33min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 27 November 2015</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Good.Dinosaur.2015.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTc5MTg2NjQ4MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzcxOTY5NjE@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOTRjZDQ0MjUtZGZjYy00ODYzLTllMzgtNzQzYTdiYzgxYmYzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjczMDkzOTA@._V1_SY1000_SX1600_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Greatest Showman</title>
<summary>Storyline
Orphaned, penniless but ambitious and with a mind crammed with imagination and fresh ideas, the American Phineas Taylor Barnum will always be remembered as the man with the gift to effortlessly blur the line between reality and fiction. Thirsty for innovation and hungry for success, the son of a tailor will manage to open a wax museum but will soon shift focus to the unique and peculiar, introducing extraordinary, never-seen-before live acts on the circus stage. Some will call Barnum's wide collection of oddities, a freak show; however, when the obsessed showman gambles everything on the opera singer Jenny Lind to appeal to a high-brow audience, he will somehow lose sight of the most important aspect of his life: his family. Will Barnum risk it all to be accepted?
PG | 1h 45min | Biography, Drama, Musical | 26 December 2017</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Greatest.Showman.2017.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Greatest.Showman.2017.1080p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI1NDYzNzY2Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODQwODczNTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,684,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmFiNzE0M2QtMjU4ZS00ZGQ0LWEyNzUtMzZkYmVjN2FjN2Y2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzk5MTY4MTU@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,766_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Grinch</title>
<summary>Storyline
For their eighth fully animated feature, Illumination and Universal Pictures present The Grinch, based on Dr. Seuss' beloved holiday classic. The Grinch tells the story of a cynical grump who goes on a mission to steal Christmas, only to have his heart changed by a young girl's generous holiday spirit. Funny, heartwarming, and visually stunning, it's a universal story about the spirit of Christmas and the indomitable power of optimism. Academy Award nominee Benedict Cumberbatch lends his voice to the infamous Grinch, who lives a solitary life inside a cave on Mt. Crumpet with only his loyal dog, Max, for company. With a cave rigged with inventions and contraptions for his day-to-day needs, the Grinch only sees his neighbors in Whoville when he runs out of food. Each year at Christmas they disrupt his tranquil solitude with their increasingly bigger, brighter, and louder celebrations. When the Whos declare they are going to make Christmas three times bigger this year, the Grinch realizes there is only one way for him to gain some peace and quiet: he must steal Christmas. To do so, he decides to pose as Santa Claus on Christmas Eve, even going so far as to trap a lackadaisical misfit reindeer to pull his sleigh. Meanwhile, down in Whoville, Cindy-Lou Who, a young girl overflowing with holiday cheer, plots with her gang of friends to trap Santa Claus as he makes his Christmas Eve rounds so that she can thank him for help for her overworked single mother. As Christmas approaches, however, her good-natured scheme threatens to collide with the Grinch's more nefarious one. Will Cindy-Lou achieve her goal of finally meeting Santa Claus? Will the Grinch succeed in silencing the Whos' holiday cheer once and for all? Find out, Christmas season 2018.
U | 1h 30min | Animation , Comedy , Family | 9 November 2018 </summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Grinch.2018.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYmE5Yjg0MzktYzgzMi00YTFiLWJjYTItY2M5MmI1ODI4MDY3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,631,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzQ2NzIzMjYwMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDAyNTk2NjM@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Kid Who Would Be King</title>
<summary>Storyline
Old school magic meets the modern world in this epic adventure. Alex (Louis Ashbourne Serkis) thinks he's just another nobody, until he stumbles upon the mythical sword in the stone, Excalibur. Now, he must unite his friends and enemies into a band of knights and, together with the legendary wizard Merlin (Sir Patrick Stewart), take on the wicked enchantress Morgana (Rebecca Ferguson). With the future at stake, Alex must become the great leader he never dreamed he could be.
PG | 2h | Adventure, Family, Fantasy | 15 February 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Kid.Who.Would.Be.King.2019.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMzOTUwNzgyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjk3MTQwNzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMzOTUwNzgyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjk3MTQwNzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Lego Batman Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
There are big changes brewing in Gotham City, and if he wants to save the city from The Joker's hostile takeover, Batman may have to drop the lone vigilante thing, try to work with others and maybe, just maybe, learn to lighten up.
U | 1h 44min | Animation, Action, Comedy | 10 February 2017</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Lego.Batman.Movie.2017.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTcyNTEyOTY0M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTAyNzU3MDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg3NDk2Mjg3OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODA2MjczMTI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,794_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Lego Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
The LEGO Movie is a 3D animated film which follows lead character, Emmet a completely ordinary LEGO mini-figure who is identified as the most "extraordinary person" and the key to saving the Lego universe. Emmet and his friends go on an epic journey to stop the evil tyrant, Lord Business.
U | 1h 40min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 14 February 2014</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2014/The%20Lego%20Movie%20%282014%29/The.Lego.Movie.2014.PROPER.720p.WEB-Dl.750MB.ShAaNiG.com.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg4MDk1ODExN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzIyNjg3MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjFkNTIyNDctOTJlZi00ZTA4LTk2MmYtYTNkYzUyZDE2MzkyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTI3MDk3MzQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Lego Movie 2: The Second Part</title>
<summary>Storyline
It's been five years since everything was awesome and the citizens are facing a huge new threat: Lego Duplo invaders from outer space, wrecking everything faster than they can rebuild.
U | 1h 46min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 8 February 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Lego.Movie.2.The.Second.Part.2019.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkyOTkwNDc1N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzkyMzk3NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkyOTkwNDc1N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzkyMzk3NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Lego Ninjago Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
Six young ninjas Lloyd, Jay, Kai, Cole, Zane and Nya are tasked with defending their island home, called Ninjago. By night, they're gifted warriors, using their skills and awesome fleet of vehicles to fight villains and monsters. By day, they're ordinary teens struggling against their greatest enemy: high school.
U | 1h 41min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 13 October 2017</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/The%20LEGO%20Ninjago%20Movie%20%282017%29/The.Lego.Ninjago.Movie.2017.720p.BRRip.950MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDI3MDljMTQtYzBiYS00NDk2LTlhYzUtYmM0NWIyMmZkMDZkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjk5NDA3OTk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,703,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMDgwMDI2ZDMtNTI4ZC00OGFhLTg4MzItNWY4MzgyNzIyZjA0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc1Nzc1NTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Lion King</title>
<summary>Storyline
A young lion prince is cast out of his pride by his cruel uncle, who claims he killed his father. While the uncle rules with an iron paw, the prince grows up beyond the Savannah, living by a philosophy: No worries for the rest of your days. But when his past comes to haunt him, the young prince must decide his fate: Will he remain an outcast or face his demons and become what he needs to be?
U | 1h 28min | Animation, Adventure, Drama | 7 October 1994</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Series/Lion%20King/The.Lion.King.1994.480p.Farsi.Dubbed.2dooble.Film9.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Series/Lion%20King/The.Lion.King.1994.720p.Farsi.Dubbed.2dooble.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Series/Lion%20King/The.Lion.King.1994.1080p.Farsi.Dubbed.2dooble.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bKPtXn9n4M4s8vvZrbw40mYsefB.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kZ9CKeZeKMUtrjZ7RuArjVMTDF4.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Lion King 2: Simba's Pride</title>
<summary>Storyline
Simba and Nala have a daughter, Kiara. Timon and Pumbaa are assigned to be her babysitters, but she easily escapes their care and ventures into the forbidden lands. There she meets a lion cub named Kovu and they become friends. What she and her parents do not know is that Kovu is the son of Zira - a banished follower of the now-dead Scar. She plans to raise Kovu to overthrow Simba and become the king of the Pride Lands. This tests not only Kiara and Kovu's relationship as they mature, but Simba's relationship with his daughter.
U | 1h 21min | Animation, Adventure, Family | Video 27 October 1998</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Series/Lion%20King/The.Lion.King.II.Simbas.Pride.1998.480p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film9.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Series/Lion%20King/The.Lion.King.II.Simbas.Pride.1998.720p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Series/Lion%20King/The.Lion.King.II.Simbas.Pride.1998.1080p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BY2Y3MTk2MDgtOTc1Yy00ZmFjLThlNTEtMDQ1Y2EzZmRjMzVjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjk1Njg5NTA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjIxMTAwMDUyNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDAyMDIyNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1608,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Lion King 3: Hakuna Matata</title>
<summary>Storyline
Timon and Pumbaa start to watch the original Lion King movie, but Timon keeps insisting to fast forward to when they come in, because they weren't seen in the beginning of the story or anywhere until halfway through. Pumbaa suggests telling the audience their story, which begins before Simba's journey begins. Through this, we meet Timon's mother and Uncle Max, discover why he left his meerkat colony, where he learned Hakuna Matata, how he meets Pumbaa, and the perils they encountered while searching for their dream home.
U | 1h 17min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | Video 16 February 2004</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Series/Lion%20King/The.Lion.King.3.2004.480p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film9.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Series/Lion%20King/The.Lion.King.3.2004.720p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film9.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/Series/Lion%20King/The.Lion.King.3.2004.1080p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film9.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOGZiMDQ1YTQtMGVlOC00OTJiLWFkYzMtYjdiYmY0NWM5YzVjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTg4MDk3MTQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGNiNzkyYmYtZjNhNi00NjY0LWE3YWUtYzAxOWYzOWY0NDhlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTc5MDI5NjE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Little Mermaid</title>
<summary>Storyline
In Disney's beguiling animated romp, rebellious 16-year-old mermaid Ariel is fascinated with life on land. On one of her visits to the surface, which are forbidden by her controlling father, King Triton, she falls for a human prince. Determined to be with her new love, Ariel makes a dangerous deal with the sea witch Ursula to become human for three days. But when plans go awry for the star-crossed lovers, the king must make the ultimate sacrifice for his daughter.
U | 1h 23min | Animation, Family, Fantasy | 12 October 1990</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/The%20Little%20Mermaid%20%281989%29/The.Little.Mermaid.1989.720p.BRrip.x264.GAZ.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTQ2ZGZjOGQtNDE1Mi00NWE5LTk5MDMtYzcyNjczYjhiODY4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjA0MDQ0Mjc@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,586,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjM1OTc5NzM2NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjcxMDIyNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1103,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Nightmare Before Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Jack Skellington, the pumpkin king of Halloween Town, is bored with doing the same thing every year for Halloween. One day he stumbles into Christmas Town, and is so taken with the idea of Christmas that he tries to get the resident bats, ghouls, and goblins of Halloween Town to help him put on Christmas instead of Halloween -- but alas, they can't get it quite right.
PG | 1h 16min | Animation, Family, Fantasy | 25 November 1994</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/The%20Nightmare%20Before%20Christmas%20%281993%29/The%20Nightmare%20Before%20Christmas%201993%20BRRip%20720p%20x264%20AC3.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNWE4OTNiM2ItMjY4Ni00ZTViLWFiZmEtZGEyNGY2ZmNlMzIyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMDU5NDcxNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQxNTY0NDE2Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzg2ODMyMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1618,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Nutcracker and the Four Realms</title>
<summary>Storyline
All Clara wants is a key - a one-of-a-kind key that will unlock a box that holds a priceless gift from her late mother. A golden thread, presented to her at godfather Drosselmeyer's annual holiday party, leads her to the coveted key-which promptly disappears into a strange and mysterious parallel world. It's there that Clara encounters a soldier named Phillip, a gang of mice and the regents who preside over three Realms: Land of Snowflakes, Land of Flowers, and Land of Sweets. Clara and Phillip must brave the ominous Fourth Realm, home to the tyrant Mother Ginger, to retrieve Clara's key and hopefully return harmony to the unstable world.
PG | 1h 39min | Adventure , Family , Fantasy | 2 November 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Nutcracker.And.The.Four.Realms.2018.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgzOTc0NTE3Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODY4MDgwNjM@._V1_SY1000_SX700_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOGVhZTg1ZjEtMzY2YS00NTI3LWI3YmQtNDRkNTc4NjExZmUzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM2NTY4NzU@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,951_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Nut Job</title>
<summary>Storyline
In a city park, Surly the Squirrel has finally gone too far with his latest caper . Now exiled, Surly and his rat buddy Buddy's collective nightmare on the streets ends when they discover a nut store to raid. With no other options, she arranges a deal to help in Surly's heist for the colony, even while Surly fully intends to betray it. However, there is more going on with the nut store being a front for bank robbers while Raccoon has his own agenda to ensure his own power. In the mayhem to come, Surly finds himself challenged in ways he never expected and discovering the real prize to treasure in this adventure.
U | 1h 25min | Animation , Adventure , Comedy | 1 August 2014</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2014/The%20Nut%20Job%20%282014%29/The.Nut.Job.2014.720p.BluRay.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1NjAxMDUzN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTE5NDM3MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjEyNzcyOTUwMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTE2NDU4MDE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Nut Job 2: Nutty By Nature</title>
<summary>Storyline
Surly and his friends, Buddy, Andie, and Precious, discover that the mayor of Oakton City is cracking one big hustle to build a giant amusement park, which in turn will bulldoze their home. The animals must stop the mayor, his daughter, and a mad animal control officer in order to take back the city park.
U | 1h 31min | Animation, Action, Adventure | 11 August 2017</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2017/The%20Nut%20Job%202-Nutty%20by%20Nature%20%282017%29/The.Nut.Job.2.Nutty.by.Nature.2017.720p.BRRip.850MB.MkvCage.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZTA5ZDZhMjgtNjNkOC00MzM0LWFlZmItZTM4MjJkMGEyZGQwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjM4NTM5NDY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,673,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZTRlNTdhNzYtYjRjNi00NjA4LWJmNDQtYTEzYjhiNjk3YjdiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDg2MjUxNjM@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,960_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Peanuts Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
Charlie Brown, Snoopy, and the whole gang are back in a heartwarming story. A new girl with red hair moves in across the street, and Charlie Brown falls in love. Now he tries to impress the red haired girl to make her feel like he's a winner, but Charlie Brown just can't do anything right. At the same time, Snoopy is writing a love story about his continuing battles with The Red Baron. Then Charlie Brown has accomplished something never done before. He gets a perfect score on his standardized test, but there has been a mistake. Should he tell the truth and risk losing all of his newfound popularity? Can Charlie Brown get the girl to love him or will he go back to being a nothing?
U | 1h 28min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 21 December 2015</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Peanuts.Movie.2015.720p.BrRip.Ganool.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNTE5NzMxNzkwNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTQ0Nzk5NzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZTViMjk3ODgtYjdkYS00ZTEyLWE0YWQtMTRkNmUzODhmMWJiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjA0MTc4OQ@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Queen's Corgi</title>
<summary>Storyline
This is about the adventure of Rex (Jack Whitehall), the British monarch's (Dame Julie Walters') most beloved dog, who loses track of his mistress and stumbles across a clan with dogs of all kinds confronting and fighting each other. During his epic journey to return to the Queen, Rex falls in love and discovers his true self.
PG | 1h 25min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 5 July 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Queens.Corgi.2019.720p.BrRip.GalaxyRG.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmQzNzZkZmEtYzhjMS00Y2RjLWE3MmYtZmU2MjlkMDU2ODRhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjQ3NzUxOTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,706,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDFlZDFjODQtNmVkNy00N2ZlLTg5MWYtN2E0NzdmOGU1Yjk1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc5OTMwOTQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Secret Life Of Pets</title>
<summary>Edit
Storyline
In a Manhattan apartment building, Max's life as a favorite pet is turned upside-down, when his owner brings home sloppy mongrel Duke. They must put their quarrels aside when they learn that adorable white bunny Snowball is building an army of lost pets determined to wreak revenge.
U | 1h 27min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 24 June 2016</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Secret.Life.Of.Pets.2016.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjIzMzA1OTkzNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODE3MjM4NzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZjJkOGUzNDYtMmM4OC00OWNkLWI5MzYtNTkxYTA4OTg2NzEwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzM5MTUzMTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1720,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Secret Life of Pets 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
Max faces some major changes after his owner Katie gets married and now has a child . On a family trip to the countryside, Max meets a farm dog named Rooster, and both attempt to overcome his fears. Meanwhile, Gidget tries to rescue Max's favorite toy from a cat-packed apartment, and Snowball sets on a mission to free a white tiger named Hu from a circus.
U | 1h 26min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 24 May 2019</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/The.Secret.Life.of.Pets.2.2019.480p.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/The.Secret.Life.of.Pets.2.2019.720p.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/The.Secret.Life.of.Pets.2.2019.1080p.6CH.mkv(link 3 | 720P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTA2NzM0MjA0MTJeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDk1MzYwNzYz._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,631,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTc1MmVkYzItMzM2MS00ZTIyLWI3YjUtNTdmYTNmMWJiMGM1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc5OTMwOTQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Star</title>
<summary>Storyline
In Sony Pictures Animation's THE STAR, a small but brave donkey named Bo yearns for a life beyond his daily grind at the village mill. One day he finds the courage to break free, and finally goes on the adventure of his dreams. On his journey, he teams up with Ruth, a lovable sheep who has lost her flock and Dave, a dove with lofty aspirations. Along with three wisecracking camels and some eccentric stable animals, Bo and his new friends follow the Star and become accidental heroes in the greatest story ever told - the first Christmas.
U | 1h 26min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 24 November 2017</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/The.Star.2017.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU4MDQ4NTM2N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDM1NTIzMzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmEwZGVkMWUtZGRhYS00Y2IyLThhN2QtYTY3OWVkNDI2NWMzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODEyMzI2OTE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,861_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Tinker Bell And The Great Fairy Rescue</title>
<summary>Storyline
Tinker Bell accidentally gets stuck inside a human house and befriends a little girl who believes in fairies. Tinker Bell's fairy friends go to rescue her and they believe she was captured by the little girl, until they make it to the house and Tinker Bell shows them she is a friend. Tinker Bell helps the little girl and her father fix their relationship.
U | 1h 16min | Animation, Adventure, Family | Video 13 August 2010</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2010/Tinker%20Bell%20and%20the%20Great%20Fairy%20Rescue%20%282010%29/Tinker.Bell.And.The.Great.Fairy.Rescue.2010.720p.BRrip.x264.GAZ.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTcxNDI2MzM4M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzA4OTk2Mw@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTczMjUwMzg5OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDcyMjUzMDE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Toy Story</title>
<summary>Storyline
A little boy named Andy loves to be in his room, playing with his toys, especially his doll named "Woody". But, what do the toys do when Andy is not with them, they come to life. Woody believes that his life (as a toy) is good. However, he must worry about Andy's family moving, and what Woody does not know is about Andy's birthday party. Woody does not realize that Andy's mother gave him an action figure known as Buzz Lightyear, who does not believe that he is a toy, and quickly becomes Andy's new favorite toy. Woody, who is now consumed with jealousy, tries to get rid of Buzz. Then, both Woody and Buzz are now lost. They must find a way to get back to Andy before he moves without them, but they will have to pass through a ruthless toy killer, Sid Phillips.
PG | 1h 21min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 22 March 1996</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/Toy.Story.1995.1080p.BrRip.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMDU2ZWJlMjktMTRhMy00ZTA5LWEzNDgtYmNmZTEwZTViZWJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQ2OTk4MzI@._V1_SY1000_SX670_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjk1NjgzMzc1MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzk0MjIyNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1662,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Toy Story 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
While Andy is away at summer camp Woody has been toynapped by Al McWiggin, a greedy collector and proprietor of "Al's Toy Barn"! In this all-out rescue mission, Buzz and his friends Mr. Potato Head, Slinky Dog, Rex and Hamm springs into action to rescue Woody from winding up as a museum piece. They must find a way to save him before he gets sold in Japan forever and they'll never see him again!
U | 1h 32min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 11 February 2000</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/Toy.Story.2.1999.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMWM5ZDcxMTYtNTEyNS00MDRkLWI3YTItNThmMGExMWY4NDIwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjUwNzk3NDc@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,677,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjE5MzgxODEyNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTA0NDU0NQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1675,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Toy Story 3</title>
<summary>Storyline
Woody, Buzz and the whole gang are back. As their owner Andy prepares to depart for college, his loyal toys find themselves in daycare where untamed tots with their sticky little fingers do not play nice. So, it's all for one and one for all as they join Barbie's counterpart Ken, a thespian hedgehog named Mr. Pricklepants and a pink, strawberry-scented teddy bear called Lots-o'-Huggin' Bear to plan their great escape.
U | 1h 43min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 19 July 2010</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/Toy.Story.3.2010.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTgxOTY4Mjc0MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTA4MDQyMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,707,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZTNkODEzMWItOTlhNi00MGFhLTg3NDYtNzUwODk1ZDIxODY2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjgwNjM5MzA@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Toy Story 4</title>
<summary>Storyline
Woody, Buzz Lightyear and the rest of the gang embark on a road trip with Bonnie and a new toy named Forky. The adventurous journey turns into an unexpected reunion as Woody's slight detour leads him to his long-lost friend Bo Peep. As Woody and Bo discuss the old days, they soon start to realize that they're two worlds apart when it comes to what they want from life as a toy.
U | 1h 40min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 21 June 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/Toy.Story.4.2019.720p.BrRip.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYzMDM4NzkxOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzM1Mzg2NzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjBhNzc0NWEtZjk0Mi00OGM5LWExMzUtMjYwOGNjM2I4ZmE0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzIwNDA4NzI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Trolls</title>
<summary>Storyline
From the creators of Shrek comes the most smart, funny, irreverent animated comedy of the year, DreamWorks' Trolls. This holiday season, enter a colorful, wondrous world populated by hilariously unforgettable characters and discover the story of the overly optimistic Trolls, with a constant song on their lips, and the comically pessimistic Bergens, who are only happy when they have trolls in their stomach. Featuring original music from Justin Timberlake, and soon-to-be classic mash-ups of songs from other popular artists, the film stars the voice talents of Anna Kendrick, Justin Timberlake, Russell Brand, James Corden, Kunal Nayyar, Ron Funches, Icona Pop, Gwen Stefani, and many more. DreamWorks' TROLLS is a fresh, broad comedy filled with music, heart and hair-raising adventures. In November of 2016, nothing can prepare you for our new Troll world.
U | 1h 32min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 21 October 2016</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/t/Trolls.2016.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTkxNDc3OTcxMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODk2NjAzOTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,673,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzU2ZjFiYmYtMzA0Ny00NTgzLTgxY2MtNzk1NTlmZGMyMTk5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQxNjcxNQ@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,753_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>UglyDolls</title>
<summary>Storyline
The free-spirited UglyDolls confront what it means to be different, struggle with their desire to be loved, and ultimately discover that you don't have to be perfect to be amazing because who you truly are is what matters most.
U | 1h 27min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 16 August 2019</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/UglyDolls.2019.480p.RMTeam.mkv(link 1 | 480P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/UglyDolls.2019.720p.6CH.RARBG.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/UglyDolls.2019.1080p.6CH.RARBG.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc0NjE2ODM2OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjQyNDUzNzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDIyYWQzN2YtYTk0Yi00ZWJhLWE5NjYtZDgzNTU0YzQ5MDRhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODEwMTc2ODQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Up</title>
<summary>Storyline
Carl Fredricksen as a boy wanted to explore South America and find the forbidden Paradise Falls. About 64 years later he gets to begin his journey along with a Boy Scout named Russel by lifting his house with thousands of balloons. On their journey they make many new friends including a talking dog and figure out that someone has evil plans. Carl soon realizes that this evildoer is his childhood idol. Will they be able to defeat him and find Paradise Falls?
U | 1h 36min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 9 October 2009</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/u/Up.2009.720p.BrRip.Ganool.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTk3NDE2NzI4NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzE1MzEyMTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,664,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZDViM2RkOWUtMjRhYS00MzlhLWJiMWItNGZiZTFjYjU3OThjL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMDU5NDcxNw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Valiant</title>
<summary>Storyline
Set in 1944, Valiant is a woodland pigeon who wants to become a great hero someday. When he hears they are hiring recruits for the Royal Homing Pigeon Service, he immediately sets out for London. On the way, he meets a smelly but friendly pigeon named Bugsy, who joins him, mainly to get away from clients he cheated in a game of find-the pebble, and helps him sign up for the war.
U | 1h 16min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 25 March 2005</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2005/Valiant%20%282005%29/Valiant%202005%20720p%20BRRip%20x264%20AAC%20-%20Ozlem.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWQ4ZDVhMDUtNTFjNi00YWE1LWI0NTMtYTZhZTFlZTE2NWY2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjIzODI5OTQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTAxNzM1NTY5MjJeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDY4MjAzMjAy._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,960_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>WALLE</title>
<summary>Storyline
In a distant, but not so unrealistic, future where mankind has abandoned earth because it has become covered with trash from products sold by the powerful multi-national Buy N Large corporation, WALL-E, a garbage collecting robot has been left to clean up the mess. Mesmerized with trinkets of Earth's history and show tunes, WALL-E is alone on Earth except for a sprightly pet cockroach. One day, EVE, a sleek (and dangerous) reconnaissance robot, is sent to Earth to find proof that life is once again sustainable. WALL-E falls in love with EVE. WALL-E rescues EVE from a dust storm and shows her a living plant he found amongst the rubble. Consistent with her "directive", EVE takes the plant and automatically enters a deactivated state except for a blinking green beacon. WALL-E, doesn't understand what has happened to his new friend, but, true to his love, he protects her from wind, rain, and lightning, even as she is unresponsive. One day a massive ship comes to reclaim EVE, but WALL-E, out of love or loneliness, hitches a ride on the outside of the ship to rescue EVE. The ship arrives back at a large space cruise ship, which is carrying all of the humans who evacuated Earth 700 years earlier. The people of Earth ride around this space resort on hovering chairs which give them a constant feed of TV and video chatting. They drink all of their meals through a straw out of laziness and/or bone loss, and are all so fat that they can barely move. When the auto-pilot computer, acting on hastily-given instructions sent many centuries before, tries to prevent the people of Earth from returning by stealing the plant, WALL-E, EVE, the portly captain, and a band of broken robots stage a mutiny.
U | 1h 38min | Animation, Adventure, Family | 18 July 2008</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2008/WALL-E.2008.720p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film2Media.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2008/WALL-E.2008.1080p.Farsi.Dubbed.Film2Media.mkv(link 3 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjExMTg5OTU0NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjMxMzMzMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE4MTcwMTM1Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTIwMzMzMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1485,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Wheely</title>
<summary>Storyline
After a really bad crash, Wheely was demoted from a rookie racer to a downtown cabbie with a mountain of debt and a bruised ego. The cause of the accident is no other than Putt Putt, his philosophical/Feng Shui practitioner fan turned to-best friend. Everything was fine until Wheely fell "head-over-wheels" over Bella, a supermodel from the upper echelons of society. To make things worse...she's got a boyfriend! Luckily for Wheely, Bella finds his street smart, ghetto-like, funny-guy character appealing.... but just before he gets the chance to get to know her better, her stuck-up boyfriend Ben, gets in the way. And that's not all.... Wheely's faced with an even bigger problem when his dream girl gets car-napped by a global syndicate masterminded by an 18-wheeler truck, Kaiser.
1h 30min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 12 October 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/w/Wheely.2018.720p.WEB-DL.YIFY.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjgzOGM1M2QtN2QxYy00MTE2LWJkMzktNzRkYTRlMTQ5ODU3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTYyOTcxNTk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,692,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjgzOGM1M2QtN2QxYy00MTE2LWJkMzktNzRkYTRlMTQ5ODU3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTYyOTcxNTk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,692,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Wonder Park</title>
<summary>Storyline
June, an optimistic, imaginative girl, discovers an incredible amusement park called Wonderland hidden in the woods. The park is full of fantastical rides and talking, funny animals - only the park is in disarray. June soon discovers the park came from her imagination and she's the only one who can fix it, so she bands together with the animals to save this magical place and bring back the wonder in Wonderland.
PG | 1h 25min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 8 April 2019</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Wonder.Park.2019.720p.mkv(link 1 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Wonder.Park.2019.1080p.6CH.mkv(link 2 | 1080P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI5MTQ5NzE4Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTk2MDA5NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,640,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2U0MmU4MDgtNTJiOC00OGIxLWI3NWEtYjk1Y2YzMjMyMjUzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc5OTMwOTQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Woody Woodpecker</title>
<summary>Storyline
The hyperactive red-headed bird enters a turf war with a big city lawyer wanting to tear down his home in an effort to build a house to flip.
PG | 1h 31min | Animation, Comedy, Family | 1 April 2018</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/w/Woody.Woodpecker.2017.720p.BrRip.RARBG.FilmZone.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDY3NjgyOTEtNDI0YS00MzRiLWFiMDUtZjY4NzQzMmQ5M2EzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkzODUwNzk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,716,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjhlMDBiYzktMDYxYi00ZjcxLTljZTgtYWM4MjQxNzg0ZjZjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzc1MTExNTk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Wreck It Ralph</title>
<summary>Storyline
Wreck-It Ralph longs to be as beloved as his game's perfect Good Guy, Fix-It Felix. Problem is, nobody loves a Bad Guy. But they do love heroes... so when a modern, first-person shooter game arrives featuring tough-as-nails Sergeant Calhoun, Ralph sees it as his ticket to heroism and happiness. He sneaks into the game with a simple plan -- win a medal -- but soon wrecks everything, and accidentally unleashes a deadly enemy that threatens every game in the arcade. Ralph's only hope? Vanellope von Schweetz, a young troublemaking "glitch" from a candy-coated cart racing game who might just be the one to teach Ralph what it means to be a Good Guy. But will he realize he is good enough to become a hero before it's "Game Over" for the entire arcade?
PG | 1h 41min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 8 February 2013</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/w/Wreck.It.Ralph.2012.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzMxNTExOTkyMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzEyNDc0OA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZDc2ZGFiZjYtY2QyYi00Yjg3LTk5YjItMGNhOGQ4ZDdkMWY4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjQ4ODE4MzQ@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,747_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Zootopia</title>
<summary>Storyline
From the largest elephant to the smallest shrew, the city of Zootopia is a mammal metropolis where various animals live and thrive. When Judy Hopps becomes the first rabbit to join the police force, she quickly learns how tough it is to enforce the law. Determined to prove herself, Judy jumps at the opportunity to solve a mysterious case. Unfortunately, that means working with Nick Wilde, a wily fox who makes her job even harder.
PG | 1h 48min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 25 March 2016</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2016/Zootopia.2016.720p.FardaDownload_net.mkv(link 1 | 720P)</sublink>
<sublink>http://s1.upload10.ir/Film/2016/Zootopia.2016.1080p.BluRay.6CH.FardaDownload_net.mkv(link 2 | 720P)</sublink>
</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTMyMjEyNzIzMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzIyNjU0NzE@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDU2OWYzMWQtNWFmYy00ZjZlLWEzN2YtMDYxY2Y3MjU1OTAyL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjk3NTUyOTc@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>