<item>
<title>Igor - 2008</title>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2008/Igor%20%282008%29/Igor%202008%20BRRip%20720p%20x264%20-MgB.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/1/1f/Igorposter.jpg/220px-Igorposter.jpg</thumbnail>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Bug's Life</title>
<summary>Storyline
At an annual pace, a huge colony of ants is forced to collect every piece of food that grows on their island for a group of menacing grasshoppers. But that all changes when a misfit inventor ant named Flik accidentally knocks over the offering pile thus forcing the grasshoppers' devious leader Hopper to force the ants to redo their gathering of food. Despite the fact that his friends don't believe him and desperate to help save the colony, Flik volunteers to go out into the world and search for a group of 'warrior' bugs. Instead, what he got was a talented group of circus performers. But when the grasshoppers return and take control of the island, Flik must prove himself a true hero before it's too late.
U | 1h 35min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 5 February 1999</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/A%20Bug%27s%20Life%20%281998%29/A.Bugs.Life.1998.720p.BluRay.x264.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNThmZGY4NzgtMTM4OC00NzNkLWEwNmEtMjdhMGY5YTc1NDE4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTgwNTQxNzM4NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTE4ODAyNw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,924_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Dog's Way Home</title>
<summary>Storyline
A female dog travels four hundred miles in search of her owner throughout a Colorado wilderness.
PG | 1h 36min | Adventure, Drama, Family | 25 January 2019</summary>
<link>http://dl2.uploadzone.ir/movies/a/A.Dogs.Way.Home.2019.720p.BrRip.MkvCage.FilmZone.mkv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5MjcwMzY5OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDM0OTI1NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjAyNGYwZGEtYWYxOS00N2UzLWI0MWUtM2YzM2YxMzQ5MjFjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkzNDYzNTk@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aladdin</title>
<summary>Storyline
Aladdin is a poor street urchin who spends his time stealing food from the marketplace in the city of Agrabah. His adventures begin when he meets a young girl who happens to be Princess Jasmine, who is forced to be married by her wacky yet estranged father. Aladdin's luck suddenly changes when he retrieves a magical lamp from the Cave of Wonders. What he unwittingly gets is a fun-loving genie who only wishes to have his freedom. Little do they know is that the Sultan's sinister advisor Jafar has his own plans for both Aladdin and the lamp.
U | 1h 30min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | 17 November 1993</summary>
<link>http://ftp.alphamediazone.com/Movies/Animation/2000-1900/Aladdin%20%281992%29/Aladdin.1992.720p.BRrip.x264.GAZ.YIFY.mp4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWFlN2VkZDQtNWY2NC00MTRmLTljMWMtOGZlNGM4ODZkNDU5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjY5NDU4NzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgzNDI3ODUyMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDg4MjY5NzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1416,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Aladdin</title>
<summary>Storyline
A kindhearted street urchin and a power-hungry Grand Vizier vie for a magic lamp that has the power to make their deepest wishes come true.
PG | 2h 8min | Adventure, Comedy, Family | 22 May 2019</summary>
<link>
<sublink>http://s2.upload10.ir/Film/New-Server/2019/Aladdin.2019.480p.P
